Good evening.
Hey! My name is Goda Takeshi.
Not giant.
Tonight's master is the world-famous ballerina, Miss Erica.
Takeshi-kun, long time no see.
Please come in…
Thanks.
… is what I want to say, but…
Sorry, my boyfriend is here right now.
Huh?
You're kidding me, Hashimoto Shinya?!
Wa-wait…
Ouch, that hurt…
It hurts more than Sumire-chan's flick on the forehead.
At this moment, I am a wandering alley dog.
Is this sensei? It's me, Shimizu.
I lost track of Takeshi-san's whereabouts again.
Yes, I apologize.
Relating the circumstances up until now…
This is only my guess, but…
Takeshi-san, who has been sleeping in a hotel around Minatoku City since mid-March
was asked by the hotel owner to pay back the hotel fees with his body.
And she demanded that he have a physical relationship with her.
Stop it, that hurts.
Oh, man… please don't!
I'll get you, you little brat!
Hey, punk! You disrespect the owner!
The men who went after him beat him to a pulp.
He was barely hanging on for dear life, and went missing.
There's no way we can find him! The owner's going to yell at us again!
And in some ways, he was saved by a young female journalist.
Welcome home!
And went to live at that woman's house.
He was very happy and his life there lasted for almost two months.
But for some reason, they had a conflict of interests and…
Never come back, you stupid pet!
He's been nowhere to be seen since last weekend.
The pet fought with you and ran away?
Yeah.
What exactly happened? In detail.
In detail?
Did he try to force himself on you or something?
No way!
No, no… it's not like that.
Then how did it happen?
It's just that, even though he's a pet, he was being really saucy with me.
Well, I was also at fault for causing the whole thing to happen.
Who seriously fights with their pet like that?
But I didn't know he was so strong…
He never disobeyed me before.
Anyway, it's fine.
I was just wondering if you could let me stay over tonight?
I knew it. You came here because you felt lonely.
That's it, right?
You can't stand the loneliness of being in that house all by yourself.
That's not how it is.
It's just that being by myself, I feel like I'm being crushed by the silence.
People call that "loneliness"!
Geez, you're so hard to love.
I know, I won't try to deny it now.
Why don't you go to your boyfriend's and seek some comfort there?
But I don't want to be a bother to senpai when he's so busy.
And that means you can be a bother to a housewife like me?
Oh, no no no… That's not what I meant at all.
I apologize. I'll go home as soon as I drink this.
Hey, can I say something that's been on my mind for a while?
Hmm?
I'll put it bluntly. Are you stupid?!
What?
You're stupid. There's something wrong with you.
If you had any common sense, there's no way this would be allowed.
Outside, you're going out with an awesome boyfriend.
But at home, you're being healed by a cute young man who is your pet.
Something that wonderful won't ever continue for long.
I don't care if you're a career woman or a Tokyo University graduate.
The one who's being conceited is not your pet, but you!
And having all that, you're still lonely and I should let you stay at my house? You've gotta be kidding me!
I'm plagued by household duties and chores and pass every day without anything that heals or rewards me.
Have you ever thought about how that might feel?
Never, right? Never!
You should just reflect on your spoiled life up until now, and feel lonely!
Oh~! Now that's off my chest.
It's not like I didn't know that…
What is it? You can talk back if you want.
I feel sorry for Hasumi-san too… having a secret like that held from him.
And for that pet.
I'm going home.
You're going home? I thought you were gonna stay for the night.
It's fine. It's not like I'm lonely or anything, and what you say is always correct.
Wait a minute.
My brother left it before he went on vacation, so can you take care of it?
This is a normal pet. Got it?
Anyway, you were going to end it someday, weren't you?
Well, I knew I couldn't let it carry on forever.
But…
He didn't have to leave like that.
Hello?
Hello, Iwaya?
Senpai…
Iwaya, what happened?
[sign]Kimi wa petto
You are my pet
7. Let's go home
Good evening.
What?
Can you just let me stay over tonight? Please?
Oh, and can I have that adult video I lent you the last time?
I haven't borrowed it!
Why are you coming to my place?
Because all the ladies turned me down.
I don't care! You and I just fought, remember?
We did?
I don't like you anymore! Go home to your lady friend!
I don't like myself either.
But I did like Momo.
Momo? Who's that?
Momo was a really good boy.
I won't let you stay over, but hang around for a while.
Are you okay?
Earlier… I thought you were crying.
Oh, no… I wasn't crying.
At that moment, they were showing a documentary on TV.
And I felt kind of moved…
Oh, was that it?
I panicked and came over right away.
Have you eaten dinner yet? Shall I fix you something?
All right, I'll have some.
Oh, Momo-chan. Long time no see.
Oh, yeah. Your birthday is the day after tomorrow, isn't it?
Oh yeah, I completely forgot.
Really?
Yes. Things have been pretty hectic lately.
I see. You must be tired.
Do you want to go out and get something good to eat?
Yes.
Only a little over one week before the performance.
Huh?
Hey, do you remember what day the 31st was?
I don't know. Isn't it just the end of the month?
That's true…
Oh, did you know that the brave youth Perseus can fly in the sky?
What? Is that my role?
He wears winged shoes and rides the flying Pegasus.
And he saves the princess who is tied naked.
A flying hero…
Sounds cool. It kind of fits you.
What?
Always flying around freely.
It's something I could never do.
Even when we're together, I feel uneasy sometimes.
She was always kind of awkward in her manner, and has loved her life in an uptight way.
Even while sleeping, she furrows her brow.
Was it a little scary?
Yes, a little…
She looked like she was in pain.
Maybe she was having a bad dream.
I hope that's what it was.
Was it the first time you spent the night together?
Yes, although we didn't have intercourse.
I don't feel the need to rush that though.
I'd rather feel stability.
Do you want to get married?
Yes, I am thinking of it.
I'm always moving around, so I want to have a place where I can settle down. That's what I've always wanted.
That makes sense.
In that aspect, she is very ideal.
Is she family-oriented?
Yes, very much so.
This morning she apologized several times, saying "I'm sorry for falling asleep",
and prepared a delicious breakfast for me.
She is very gentle, beautiful and excels in her work.
And she's flat.
Yes…
What?
Oh, I mean… I am very envious.
But I know for sure that she does not feel at peace.
I wish she'd at least open up and be herself in front of me.
But it seems difficult…
It seems like I'm losing to even a pet.
You are also feeling pressured.
That may be so, more or less.
I see.
You have a very nice smile.
You are a wonderful person.
Doctor, may I see you for a moment?
Please, go ahead.
Hello, nice to see you again.
She said she wanted to see you as soon as possible.
I'm sorry. I have an appointment after this, and I couldn't reschedule it later.
But my headaches and insomnia are as bad as ever.
What is wrong?
Actually,
my pet has disappeared again.
That's enough!
"My pet this, my pet that" is all you say!
You're an idiot of a woman who can't even understand a man's heart!
Idiot?
You, too!
To let such a woman in while I'm in the middle of a counselling session!
I'm sorry.
The worst… you two are the worst!
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
Shall we stand for a bit?
All right.
Relax, relax.
Oh… relax.
Yes, let's live life carefree.
We men always carry an unconscious pressure which women never have.
It's the result of the systematization which makes us the head of the family.
It's a given that we're strong. It's a given that we are the breadwinners.
A given that women protect the family, etc., etc.
And women rarely notice that type of pressure.
I see.
But women these days are strong-headed. It's become a difficult world for men to live in.
You may have a point.
What's wrong with liking young women with big breasts?
Women also like those ripped young men.
Is that so?
It's true!
Their desire to corrupt young men makes women today seem stronger than ever.
I see.
Then women should also take responsibility and be reprimanded.
There is no reason for men to shoulder the heavy burden by themselves.
But I want to become a support for her.
That's wrong!
You can't spoil her like that.
For you to want her to be at peace, means giving her even more pressure.
I see… I think that's true!
There's absolutely nothing wrong with you.
Now, let out all the tension in your body, and let's go.
What is it with everyone calling me stupid?
You…
You're Goda Takeshi's dance…
I'm Takeshi's ex.
What do you want with me?
I don't want anything, old lady.
Old lady?
It's really low of you to make a young man a pet when you work at such a big company.
Takeshi's not the kind of guy that should be made a pet.
He's an elite ballet dancer and has won a lot of awards since he was a kid.
Even in modern dance, he's what we all aspire to be.
If you're going to pay someone to comfort you, then go find someone else.
It's not like that. Momo is…
Who the hell is Momo?!
You're doing the same thing as those old men who surround themselves with young girls.
Elite women are the worst.
I never want to grow up to be an adult like you.
I won't let you have Takeshi.
Hmm… now I see how things are.
Of course… yes, of course.
She's… acting a little scary.
I understand. I understand now. It's exactly how everyone says things are.
What are you saying all of a sudden?
It's just a pet.
On top of that, I just lost to him, and he made me make him a pet.
I didn't even plan on keeping him that long. I don't know why I'm feeling all emotional now.
I was just taking care of an abandoned dog for two months, and that's all.
So from tomorrow onwards, I think I'm going to look forward and just enjoy myself.
Enjoy my present petless life.
Umm…
It's good to look towards the future and all, but…
I'm looking towards the future, I'm happy, and I feel very refreshed.
Now I won't have any secrets to keep from senpai either.
Then, I'll go over there to return your dog later.
I have to forget.
I must have hurt him a lot.
That time… and that time…
Don't come home.
And that time…
He won't come back anymore.
Momo is no longer in this world.
Higher.
Ruff!
Wan?
Okay, I'll become your pet.
I just needed a place to stay. A temporary place to stay until I go to Germany.
Even higher.
Anywhere was fine.
But why am I…
I can't become some kind of a hero.
That tickles, Sumire-chan.
What the… it's you!
My apologies.
Why are you here?!
I finally found you.
This is for you.
You haven't sent your application to Germany yet, have you?
She said that if you're struggling with a lack of money, she wants you to have this.
Mom did?
Yes.
Even in contemporary dance, Frankfurt Dance Theatre is very famous.
If you still have the will to continue dancing, sensei said she wants to cooperate.
It's all right.
I can get the money from welfare anyway.
Then is there a reason why you're hesitating to go on the foreign exchange?
No, nothing…
Did Dad and Mom divorce yet?
No.
So you're still helplessly in love with Mom?
What are you saying? I'm just a business-related…
Do you remember?
Pas de chat.
It was the first ballet move you taught me.
I remember.
It was when you were three.
Back then, it was just fun to dance…
But Mom and Dad were always fighting because of me.
So if the foreign exchange and competition worked out for me,
I thought that maybe they would get along better.
Takeshi, you are my pride and joy!
Whatever your father may say, I'm going to make you continue ballet.
Takeshi, make your mother's dream come true.
The joy of meeting the expectations of the person you love.
But the expectation kept growing, and it became a monster.
The joy transformed into the fear of letting that person down.
I just didn't understand after a while…
the reason I was dancing for.
But Takeshi-san, you were always my bird of hope.
What a good boy, Momo.
I just wanted a hand that would accept me.
What?
I'm not sure either.
Please go see your mother before going to Germany.
You haven't seen her in four years.
I'm going to have a performance soon.
It's contemporary dance, which Mom hates.
Tell her to come see if she wants.
As I explained earlier, the situation is like this…
What is that? A complaint call?
It's from the same guy. He's so persistent.
About that, like I've been saying…
He hung up on me.
Damn it…
If he calls again, let me answer it.
With people like that, it's better if a man yells at them.
Yeah, you should just leave it to him.
No, it's fine. It's concerning my own article, so I'll deal with it myself.
You're really not cute. That's why it doesn't work.
What do you mean, it doesn't work?
What?
Can you explain to me in detail, why it doesn't work?
I can understand if I was avoiding the blame, but I'm trying to take the responsibility here.
I don't understand why I have to be talked to like this.
It's not like we need you to take on all the responsibilities by yourself.
We can do just fine without you.
Oh my gosh! Is that you, Fukushima-san?
Oh! It's you, Iwaya-san.
Did you forget to wash your face before you came?
What kind of a joke is that?
I just came to fix my makeup.
In the afternoon, my foundation starts coming off.
Would you like to try it too, Iwaya-san? Maybe you'll look a little prettier.
Unfortunately, I'm too busy and don't have such time to waste.
I guess elite people don't have to worry about trying so hard.
Although it must feel good to work hard and raise your career.
So what? There are many people who can take your place.
I'm me. I just do things the way I see fit.
I know you're actually not that strong.
That woman frustrates me so much.
Calm down, chief.
Due to hormonal imbalance, women's ups and downs are apparently more extreme.
That's why I don't want to work with women.
Well, you'll never know how long she'll be working here.
What do you mean?
I heard that Hasumi-kun may return to Rio de Janeiro again in the near future.
Is that true?
Rio de Janeiro's Yoshimoto-san collapsed, right? So he may have to go in his place.
I wonder what that woman is going to do then.
Hasumi-san is…?
[sign]Nioi-sumire (violets)
Hey, you…
You're Iwaya-san's…
Sumire-chan's ex-boyfriend?
Welcome.
This is the pet advice room.
What happened to Momo-chan?
No, that doesn't matter anymore.
What do you mean?
It's fine. The pet got sick of me and ran away. That's all.
Got sick of you?
What are you laughing about?
I've never heard of a case where the pet got sick of its master.
It's not like a man-woman relationship.
What?
Didn't I tell you?
Between a pet and a master, there's a relationship of superiority and inferiority.
That's why the pet will never betray its master,
and it's also why the master feels the responsibility to care for the pet.
The pet also needs you.
The only person in the world that can protect the pet is its master.
There is no one to replace them.
Oh, doctor…
I'm really sorry about what happened with Iwaya-san.
No, I was the one who was being rude… it was my fault.
I can only be grateful for your return, despite all the awful things I said.
Umm…
This weekend, would you like to walk our dogs together?
What?!
I came back here because my wife's giving birth.
I see…
So you're going to be a father soon.
Oh yeah, your flowers were blooming.
Nioi-sumire?
I see…
I gave it to her right around this time last year… for her birthday.
Umm… there's something that's been on my mind.
You're one of those… guys that live off a woman's money, right?
No, I'm a pet.
Well, I guess that's worse because it means I'm pretty much useless.
I want her to be happy.
I don't want you to do anything that would hurt her.
Well, I probably wouldn't hurt her as much as you did.
That's true, but…
I just wanted to be together.
If I became her pet, I could stay by her side.
Although there was no sex involved, she needed me more than any other human.
Not human?
Yup, I have no human rights.
Isn't that kind of hard?
It may have been hard…
Yeah, sometimes it was super hard…
But sometimes I was super happy. So I needed her, too.
It sounds like a surreal story to me.
Maybe…
But it was a lot more pure than any real love relationship.
You aren't such a bad person after all.
You aren't either.
Please take care of Iwaya-san. She's actually a very fragile person.
She never showed me her efforts nor her tears, but she was probably holding in a lot…
At first, she didn't even know how to cook.
I don't know when she started practicing, but she soon became like a professional chef.
I see…
So the cooking was indebted to you.
What?
I'm getting a bit jealous.
Hello?
Oh, really?! I'll be right there!
What happened?
My wife is starting to have contractions.
I'm glad we got to meet again.
Congrats! Be a good papa to the baby.
Tell Iwaya-san "Congratulations", too!
Huh?
Because her birthday is tomorrow!
Momo!
Momo?
Momo…
He wouldn't be in a place like that, would he?
I told you, you didn't have to come along with me.
It's fine. I'll help you when you're in need.
I'm the only girl friend you have.
What do you mean by that?
Honestly, there are some things I envied about you.
You're beautiful, elite, and have everything.
As for me, I'm always tied up at home.
Personally, I'd like to see what happens between you and that pet.
Thanks, Yuri-chan.
Oh, I'm tired… I'm so exhausted.
We can't find him after all.
Even though I mustered up the courage to come to places
like Ikebukuro and Shibuya, where all the young people seem to gather.
Really…
I'm sorry, Yuri-chan. Thanks.
Momo?
What was I thinking, there's no way he'd fit into a small box like this.
Is something wrong?
Nothing…
Well I'll be darned, it's an abandoned kitty.
There, there…
Excuse me, what are you planning to do with that?
I'm going to find the owner.
It's a shame that there are so many irresponsible owners out there.
There, there…
I'm sorry…
I'm sorry, Momo.
Momo.
Let's go home.
Let's go back home, Momo.
Come here.
If I take this hand now,
I'll go back to being Momo again.
That sweer, but bitter life as a pet.
Momo.
It's okay that I come back?
It's okay.
Let's go home together.
Do you have somewhere else to go?
I don't have anywhere.
Only your place, Sumire-chan…
Yours is the only place… I can go home to.
I don't mind if I don't get treated like a human.
Because in front of these tears,
I can become a courageous hero.
This feels great~
I wonder where he has been, getting so dirty.
Oh, it's past 12!
Sumire-chan!
Happy birthday! Here's your present.
A shampoo certificate?
Yup! I thought that once in a while, in return for your daily care, I could gently massage your scalp.
Like I need that.
What?! Isn't that a little harsh?
I took the time to write it with all my heart.
It's not harsh. What is "bathing suit recommended" supposed to mean?
Oh, my gosh! It's Destroyer King Hashimoto Shinya's autograph!
Oh, yeah. I got punched a little, but he was a really good guy.
Wow, Momo! It's great that you got punched! You got this!
Where did you meet him?! That's awesome!
Where I met him is a secret…
Hello?
Happy birthday! Sorry to call you all of a sudden.
I got out of work early, so is it all right if I go over now?
Umm… well…
Right now is a little…
My younger sister is over right now and she wants to stay the night.
I'm sorry.
No, it's my fault for asking all of a sudden. I guess I'll see you in the day then.
Shall we wait for twelve more hours?
It's okay, right? We're going to see each other in twelve hours anyway.
I love you, Sumire-chan!
Wait… don't jump on me like that! Your hair's wet!
Don't make such a fuss! Then dry my hair for me!
Do it yourself!
So you went back to your master?
Yup. Right now, she's on a date with her boyfriend.
I see…
Takeshi~, one of your fans is here again.
Oh, all right. Thanks.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
You're Goda Takeshi, right?
Yes.
This is a birthday present for you.
Thank you very much.
Open it.
Yes.
I'm going to ask you directly.
Are you really that woman's pet?
Yes, directly back at you.
You don't hesitate to answer immediately, do you?
Nope, I don't.
By the way, who are you?
Then did you know that today, Hasumi-san is going to propose to that woman?
I want you to marry me.
There's a possibility that I may return to Rio de Janeiro in the fall.
If that were to happen, I'd want you to come with me.
It's accurate information.
I know that he bought her a ring from Bank Reef.
If that were to happen, wouldn't you get thrown away?
I see. And just what do you want me to do?
You catch on fast. Then I'll be straight with you.
I want Hasumi-san.
So I want you to steal that woman away from him.
If you don't know how to do it, I can teach you.
Oh, I get it.
You can't win just by being on the offensive, so you're trying to break things from the inside.
Wow, you're really serious about Hasumi-kun. You're kinda cute.
I'm not serious about him. I just want him, that's all.
So you seem to be pretty smooth with girls.
Then why don't you do something about her?
If I could get her like that, I would have done it already.
But she doesn't seem to want that, and maybe I don't either.
Hey, do you know what the kite's joy is?
When I say kite, I mean the kind you fly for New Years.
The reason for the kite to fly happily in the sky is not because it's free.
It's because there's a string that will eventually tug it close.
Even if it could fly freely, no matter how high it flew… even if it could reach outer space, it wouldn't be happy.
I don't understand the point you're trying to make at all.
Beyond that string is a place to go home to.
Even if it gets tattered and torn, or becomes useless.
There is a gentle hand that will hold it close.
That's why I can fly.
For that, I would live the rest of my life as a useless creature.
Thanks for the treat, even though I didn't drink anything.
So I want you to steal that woman away from him.
I don't have to be told by you.
I will never let go of that hand.
I'm not in a rush, but I just want an answer.