Hey, my name is Ooishi Minori.
The landlord of this place, Mon Paradis.
My duty is to always see my residents off cheerfully.
But this morning, I don't feel so good.
Who would litter like this…
Excuse me, Mr. Landlord.
Oh, it's Kusunoki-san from apartment 407! Good morning!
Thank you.
Umm… it may just be a mistake on my part,
but I heard there's someone on our floor who has a pet.
What! A pet?!
Oh, no. I don't think I can stop now.
Ouch!
What are you doing?
Don't whine! I told you, no kissing!
But you were sleeping so peacefully and looked so cute.
What?
I won't do it again. Sorry.
You're the real thing, right?
You really, really are Momo, aren't you? You came back?
Sumire-chan?
Thank goodness! I was so worried about you!
I'm home!
I have…
a boy as a pet.
I found him wounded and soaked by the rain.
His name is Momo.
Momo doesn't complain about the fact that he is shorter than me,
has no educational background, or has less income than me.
This is because he is simply my pet.
Nice to meet you, Master.
I don't want you to misunderstand.
I may be taking care of him, but that's all there is to it.
Meaning there is nothing between us in terms of sex.
Because even if a pet is male, it's not a man.
Recently, I also got a boyfriend.
Hasumi-senpai, whom I've always admired.
I thought he was out of my league, but…
You said you weren't planning on seeing anyone for a while.
Is it all right if I go meet your pet?
Now I am constantly busy with my pet,
and trying to become a better woman for my boyfriend.
Everyday is like a battle.
Your meals really are the best.
Hey, if you're going to leave a letter behind, put it someplace where I can find it easily.
Sorry.
Do you have a cold?
Mmm… I've not been feeling very well lately.
That's because you don't sleep under the blankets properly.
The house dust at the hotel I was staying in was awful.
Hotel?
Yeah, I was in Takazaki.
For a dance seminar.
Oh, I see.
After you finish that, why don't you take some medicine and go to sleep again?
If you don't get more rest, you'll develop asthma again.
What?
Hey,
are you happy when I'm around?
Huh?
You look like you're having fun today.
Not particularly.
Because you ate so happily, the mood just got carried away.
What are you doing? You're in the way!
I'm just happy that you're so worried about me.
From now on, I'll wait patiently for you to come home every day.
Next time you're gone, I'll put a dog tag on you.
I wouldn't mind.
A lot has happened, but I have no complaints. I'm happy with my current life.
I hope that these bright days will continue.
It's decided. I'm going on that exchange programme to Germany.
I'm going to leave in June.
Give sensei my regards.
Takeshi-san…
That's all. Goodbye.
You are my pet
4. Love infection
Shiba dog, Husky, Maltese, Beagle.
Corgi, German Shepherd, Yorkshire Terrier.
Poodle and Border Collie.
French Bul and Cocker Spaniel.
And don't forget the longhaired Chihuahua, Pitt-kun.
It almost sounds like we're naming flowers.
You're right that dogs have soft names.
Their names ofter begin with H and R sounds.
Soft things have the power to heal one's heart.
Soft things?
Yes.
Soft things, little things, warm things.
The human brain is programmed to feel healed by such things.
Soft, little and warm.
Yes.
Is that so?
Oh?
That movie was good.
Yeah, I was moved to tears.
I have a soft spot for movies like that.
If I had been watching it alone at home, I would have been sobbing.
Me too.
Especially movies about animals and children.
Oh! I remember you bawling while you were reporting about a hippopotamus giving birth.
Please don't bring that up!
Oh!
Thanks goodness! We still have time. It was at three o'clock, right?
Oh, the speech by the Austrian president.
With our current work shifts, I always have night duty when you get days off.
"Our"…
Let's go. We have to make the best out of the next hour and a half.
Wow, they look like models! Such a picture perfect couple, don't you agree?
Kokeshi doll.
What?
Stiff. Iwaya-san is too stiff.
You think so?
She and I…
What am I going to do? This is a dilemma.
The area beneath my left ear is itching.
But if I scratch it with my right hand, my posture will look very awkward.
Plus, I'm carrying a purse. Worse still, it's colorful.
But… There's no way I can let go of this hand.
I'll ignore it. Just don't think about it.
Oh, Iwaya.
Why don't we try that?
What? Sticker photos?
Actually, I don't even have a single one.
Personally, I don't really like taking photos.
There! I've inserted money inside.
I wonder what they mean by preferred pose?
Do you think there might actually be someone inside these machines?
What?
Oh…
Wha… What can this be?
Shall we decide on pink?
Oh, it turned pink! Look!
Oh, our faces are somehow on the screen.
Oh, there's the camera!
Wa… Wait!! That… just now…
Wow! The colors are pretty vivid in these things.
I'm sorry. I'm not very good with photos.
Really?
That's the worst. I want to throw it away. I would like to erase it.
That bad? It reminds me of the time back then.
What?
The time when we took a photo together back in Kofu.
When you came to see me off to Rio de Janeiro…
I still treasure that picture.
Treasure…
I'm so sorry!
What?
Oh, nothing. I was very happy to be able to see you off.
I wonder where I should stick this.
This half is for you.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Are you all right? You're not sick, are you?
It's rather breezy today.
Oh, no. Not at all. Please excuse me for a moment.
Excuse me.
I should get rid of the smell.
Thank you for your hard work.
Maybe I do have a cold.
Are you okay? If you want, I have some nasal decongestant.
Thanks, Junpei. I love you.
Me too.
Oh, so we love each other.
No, no, no.
I just thought about how proud I should be, that a friend of mine could get into the International Contemporary Dance Competition.
I'm so proud, yet a little envious too.
You can jump so high and you have sucha a beautiful girl worrying about you.
It feels like it's healed.
Whenever Rumi calls, it's always about you.
I'm envious of you, too. Of your…
When you take happiness for granted, you become greedier and greedier.
It's the sad saga of humanity.
In that sense, pets are nice and simple.
But don't pets sometimes become greedy, too?
They do.
But if a pet became too greedy, they would just be abandoned.
And because they understand that fully, they'll listen obediently to what their master says.
It's going to be okay, you know?
Don't worry, Takeshi. It's going to be okay.
I shouldn't have worn new shoes.
I'm sorry. Thank you so much.
Oh, here. It looked good so I got it.
Can you move towards the edge a little more?
What?
Like this?
Senpai, our coworkers might see us.
I don't mind if we're seen.
We don't have any policy against office romances.
Are you sure you have the time for this?
He fell asleep.
There, there…
What am I doing…
When I'm like this, I feel really calm.
Oh, that's mine. I'm sorry, I think it's from the office.
Shiorin?
I wonder who it is… Maybe Shiohara-san?
I don't know. I've never heard anyone call Shiohara-san "Shiorin".
That's true.
Hello?
Oh, I was wondering who it was!
Really? That's awful. Are you okay?
You shouldn't get involved anymore.
Just leave it alone, and it'll be better for you too.
Okay, later.
No, now is not a good time.
I have night duty.
Tomorrow? I really don't know about then…
I'm really sorry, I'll hear about it some other time, so…
Yes.
I'm sorry, she just kept talking so I couldn't find a good time to cut her off.
Oh no, that's fine.
It was from Fukushima-san.
What?! Fukushima-san?
Apparently, she broke up with her boyfriend recently.
And he keeps following her around and she's been seeking advice from me.
Oh…
The other day, I was having lunch with her at the company cafeteria.
She didn't know how to use the company cell phone, so she asked me for help.
And then, apparently she entered her own number into my phone. I'm so surprised.
Yes, what a surprise.
No matter how you look at that, it's a made-up story.
I think it's safe to say that the enemy has the upper hand.
The "enemy"…?
She's an enemy!
My head hurts. Don't you see?
I do see! Last time, she tried to break up our date directly.
Besides, you've been going out with this guy for two weeks already,
and you haven't let him into your pants yet.
You shouldn't say such things in front of a child!
She doesn't understand, so it's fine.
If you don't act quick, she'll steal him with sex.
But…
Wait, are you sick?
I don't know, I'm getting the chills.
Sumire-chan! I cleaned up, so forgive me!
No, five more minutes. Clean from corner to corner.
He left the toilet seat up, so I'm punishing him.
To enforce punishment immediately after a wrongdoing is the fundamentals of discipline.
But I wonder if Fukushima-san really likes Hasumi-senpai.
You're too nonchalant, Sumire.
You can't just wait around and expect to still be connected.
The relationships between men and women aren't that simple!
Why don't you invite him for a change?
Like, "Umm… Is it okay if I go over to your place next time?"
I can't say such a shallow phrase.
Stop trying to keep that cool façade!
I'm not trying to look cool.
That's really not cute, that side of you.
You can't even smoke a cigarette in front of senpai.
What kind of a relationship are you in,
when you can't even be yourself in front of your boyfriend?
It's not that I can't show my true self.
Hey, hey, Sumire-chan!!
Should I arrange the pads in order from heavy to light?
Huh? No, don't touch those!
Wait, Momo.
I guess she shouldn't be herself too much in front of him.
Looks like it's around 37.2 degrees Celsius.
I thought it was just another one of those headaches.
I might have passed on my cold to you.
Maybe.
What?
Are you that happy that I'm sick?
Nope.
I'm just drunk with the thought that I've infected you with my virus.
What's that supposed to mean?
Hey, did you hurt yourself?
Yeah, a blister.
From walking too much in my new shoes.
The pair you bought for your date!
Hey, I'm not sick anymore, so can I sleep next to you?
Huh? Why? No, you can't! Get out now! Scram!
Yes.
Take care, master.
Later.
Was I that scary?
Okay! The other papers haven't gotten hold of that news yet, have they?
No matter what, I want to publish it in the morning papers. We'll handle the editing.
Thank you!
Come to think of it…
I knew it.
Setaya's 15-year old: Goda Takeshi
I feel terrible.
That's a lie!
It's true! She kept looking at me.
What are you talking about?
I feel love in the air…
She doesn't seem to have a care in the world.
Iwaya, have you gotten that story about the vaccine ready for next week?
Oh, I'll turn it in before the conference meeting,
along with the review for Dr. Ogawa's novel.
That's done, too? That's fast of Dr. Ogawa.
Yes. I'll bring it together.
So cyborgs get sick, too.
What?
Don't give it to me. The masks are sold in the drugstore upstairs.
Yes, thank you.
Uriyama-san!
What is it?
I finally found Carlos!
That's great.
She's a beauty! I put her on my screen.
Well, it's just an ordinary cat.
That's awful! Hasumi-san told me she was cute!
He's nice to everyone.
Huh?
Shoot, I forgot the floppy!
Is this it?
Yes, thank you.
Oh, and this is the medicine you have to take with lunch. You left it on the table.
I totally forgot to take it.
Are you okay? You were out of sorts in the morning, too.
Yeah… I think I'll go home early today.
Oh, yeah. Here.
It's a reward. Open it when you get home.
Wait… What?
What?
Don't kiss me in public!
But I'm so happy!
Iwaya-san?
Ishida-kun.
Oh, err… Umm…
Uh… A young boyfriend?
No… This is… Umm…
Nice to meet you. I'm her younger brother, Takeshi.
Oh, your younger brother?!
Yes. Thank you for always looking out for my older sister.
Huh? Oh, yes…
He just came back from France, so he's a little touchy-feely.
Oui, bonjour!
Oh, so that's what it was! I was so surprised!
I was surprised as well.
Our hometown is in Chiba, but my sister wanted me to stop by here. So I was just stopping by.
Right, sis?
Yes, Takeshi.
But you look nothing like Iwaya-san.
What?
Is that so?
Maybe because I look more like my mother.
That must be it.
Iwaya-san has Hasumi-san from External Affairs, so there should be no such thing as…
Oh, no.
Well, I'll be heading back now.
You're lucky to have such a wonderful sister.
Let's take good care of her.
Thank you for your hard work, Hamada-san!
Merci beaucoup, monsieur.
Who looks like my mother?
That Ishida-kun seems to be interested in you.
What? Are you serious?!
But it's true that I have a sister in Chiba. Actually three.
Three sisters? But my hometown is in Yokohama.
Oh, really?
But I'm relieved that we didn't spill the beans.
I don't know what I'd do if people found out I had a boy as a pet.
That's true.
Oh, thanks for this. Good luck at your lessons.
Bye.
And… I don't want to be repetitive, but please follow the deadlines.
All right, that's it.
Thank you for your hard work!
Oh, my throat hurts.
Hasumi-senpai!
Why are you here?
Can I have a moment with you?
See you later.
All right, later.
I heard from Junpei.
You're living with a career woman right now, aren't you?
Yeah, but it's more like…
So you live off her money like a pimp?
I'm her pet.
What's that? That's worse, you're not even a human.
That may be true.
Did you break up with me because you wanted to be with her?
Huh? What does that mean?
You were the one who broke up with me.
I just thought that if I said I wanted to break up,
you would say that you don't want to, and like me even more.
That's so unreasonable. You're hard to understand.
Then kiss me.
Are you going home now?
Yeah, things were kind of hectic in the morning, with the news from Palestine.
That must have been difficult.
Kuraki-san told me,
that you were sick.
What?
I was worried that it was because I dragged you around the other day.
Not at all. It's really nothing.
No, but that day…
it seemed like there was something wrong.
Really, there wasn't. You don't have to worry.
Of course I'd worry.
It seems like you're constantly worrying about satisfying me.
You know, maybe because I was your senior back at Kofu.
No, it's not like that.
It may not be such a big deal…
But the fact that I was the only one who didn't know about your sickness…
It made me a little sad.
You can be more personal with me.
I'm sorry.
No. If you apologize, it will make me feel worse.
Hasumi-san.
Fukushima-san.
I'm sorry for calling you so often.
After calling you yesterday, it got even worse!
He kept bothering me and bothering me with phone calls.
And I'm scared, so…
Would it be okay if I stayed at your place tonight?
Huh?
When I saw your personal particulars, I noticed you live really close to me.
I live on the 4th block, along Meiji Road.
Oh, really?
Yes!
And I felt that we had some sort of connection,
and I actually still feel…
Umm, I'll be going now.
What?
I still have some work left to do. So please, take your time. Goodbye.
Iwaya.
Iwaya-san is so cool.
I can't be strong like that.
I still like you, Takeshi.
Do you like me?
Yeah, I like you.
People will come by here. Let's go somewhere else.
Well, I can't take you to a love hotel. I don't have any money.
Then I'll pay.
And even if we go, I'll leave in half an hour's time.
It's around the time that she'll be coming home.
Do you still want to go? Or do you want to continue here?
You're mean! I hope you die!
What's wrong, Rumi?
Junpei!
Is it Takeshi again?
Takeshi-san is scheduled to leave at the beginning of June.
Yes, I checked with the organization.
They're a pretty well-known group in Frankfurt.
Yes, the period is to be about three years.
How about it, sensei? Why don't you sit down and talk to Takeshi beforehand?
Oh… Well, I will contact you later.
Oh, so pets are not allowed here?
Yes. It was on the move-in brochure, wasn't it?
Have you not read it?
I did read it. It was the fourth column on the fourth page.
Yeah!
Oh… Iwaya-san, may I have a moment?
Oh, I'll be going.
That woman is always so unfriendly.
Excuse me…
I would like to know a little more about that young woman.
I'm home.
Momo, you're not home again? You told me you'd be waiting every day.
What are you doing?
Momo!
Oh… Sumire-chan, welcome home!
I was thinking about something, and I guess I fell asleep.
What a strange child.
Thanks!
I was very happy with my reward.
It's not much.
I just thought it was inconvenient that I couldn't get in touch with you sometimes.
I'm tired. Is retort good enough?
It's fine, I can make it myself.
I'll just eat the frozen curry we had last time.
Aren't you going to eat anything?
I don't have an appetite.
Did something happen with your boyfriend?
What?! Why?
I wonder why…
For some reason, I can always tell what you're thinking about.
What do you mean?
Because I'm a pet, I think it's an animal's instinct.
Come to think of it, Momo…
My dog, Momo…
Whenever I was down, it would always be by my side.
There were a lot of things that got me depressed.
My parents were always fighting with each other,
and my grandfather disciplined us strictly.
My parents were always fighting, too.
Really?
Yup.
My mother wanted me to do ballet,
and my father ridiculed men going into ballet.
Always fighting!
I see.
But my older sisters always took good care of me.
I can imagine.
You finally smiled.
I think you should relax more.
When people like each other, they're supposed to have more fun.
Have fun?
Yeah.
They're supposed to say "I love you" over and over like idiots,
kiss each other, and sleep with each other…
I can't be like those idiotic couples!
Idiotic couples are good.
Because if you think too deeply, it'll hurt.
Easier said than done.
It's easy!
I like you.
See? Like that, it's easy.
Ouch! Why'd you hit me?
I just felt like it… You just made me mad.
Hey, your cheeks are red.
What?
It's my fever. I have a fever! I'm sick, remember?
Are you going to sleep in those clothes?
I'm fine, just leave me alone!
All right, I got it.
Gosh…
You're a pet, don't exert weird pheromones…
Hello?
This is my phone number.
Make sure you record it in your phone.
Okay.
Can you wake me up around eleven?
I need to take my medicine.
Gotcha.
Tomorrow will be better.
I'm sure.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Good night.
I like you.
No way. I can't say it. I've never said anything like that in my life.
It sounds like the lyrics to some pop song.
Hey, wasn't today's hamburger rice delicious?
The omelette rice was really good too! Let's go again. Yeah, let's go again.
Oh yeah, we overheard
Iwaya-san and Hasumi-san talking on the rooftop the other day.
And on top of that, it was like "Enter Fukushima-chan!"
And then Iwaya-san just left…
And… and…?
Hasumi-san told Fukushima-chan,
"Sorry, I'm planning on spending my days off with my girlfriend."
How dreamy…
Sorry, I'm planning on spending my days off with my girlfriend.
Your girlfriend?
Yes, with Iwaya.
And, I have a policy not to let anyone but my girlfriend into my home.
Well, I'll call you again.
The way he was firm was attractive, too.
What a happy idiot I am…
Hasumi-senpai!
Iwaya…
What's up?
I…
I'm so sorry about the last time.
And…
And… senpai, you have tomorrow off, right?
Umm…
I can take many days off this month,
so I was thinking I might take the day off tomorrow.
And…
And… Umm…
Then will you come over?
What?
Tonight, to my place.
Yes!
Oh…
Look, I stuck it on right away.
Oh, no! I hate this ugly-faced picture.
Huh? You look cute!
I like how you look. Like you're not putting up any kind of façade.
Is your cold better?
Oh yes, I'm all better.
Then, I'll be looking forward to tonight.
Yes.
Good night.
Thank you, you too.
I want to be more like myself around him.
Iwaya-san.
Oh… Doctor, why are you here?
I was about to go home.
Overtime by yourself, I see?
Yes, just a little more.
I left early yesterday because I had a cold.
I see.
Well, you are truly very hardworking and beautiful.
That's not so…
I saw you at the park the other day.
Huh? When?
Probably the day you got that blister.
Why?
You and I are alike.
Huh? What do you mean by that?
Well, how do I say…
I can love what the world is supposed to love, such as pets, mothers and children…
But I cannot love a woman.
What does that mean?
You are the same.
You cannot wholeheartedly surrender your heart to a man.
And won't let them heal you.
Me?
You cannot love a man.
Am I not right?
No, I don't quite understand what you're trying to say.
Oh, Natasha-chan!
My escort has arrived. This is enough talking for today.
What? What were you talking about just now?
Did you hear that the host server went down?
The host server?
Yes, apparently beyond volume 13, all typing has to be done over again.
Are you serious?
Oh, Iwaya-san.
The host server just went down and an extra server is in full rotation,
but the news section gets priority.
What?
You may not be able to go home tonight.
Well, I'll be going now.
I have to do everything over?
I can't believe this.
All set!
She's early.
Coming!
You…?
Hey, Fukushima-san?
I'm sorry…
I know it's rude, but I never would have thought that he would be waiting at my place like that.
I didn't know what to do after that.
Anyway, I came running here as fast as I could.
I see.
Well, after a little while, I'll walk you home.
He'll probably be gone by then.
No!
What?
I don't want to be in that house by myself. I'm scared.
May I stay here tonight?
That, I can't…
Please!
I'll get killed.
I'm coming, I'm coming!
Hello, Sumire-chan?
Momo?
I might not be able to come home tonight, so don't stay up for me.
What?! Again?
I can't help it, I have work.
But I'm lonely! Hey, I'm hungry!
There's 1000 yen in the usual spot, so go buy something to eat.
I'm going to hang up now.
Man…
This pisses me off.
Shoot, I'm getting even lonelier.
Senpai won't answer the phone…
I wonder if he fell asleep.
Hasumi-senpai?
Who is this?
Iwaya's phone is busy…
What am I going to do?
Was she on the 4th floor?
You…
I must have had the wrong number.
Plus I just hung up on her, I was so rude.
That can't be…
Hello?
Iwaya-san?
This is Fukushima~