I want you to marry me.
I want you to steal that woman from him.
I don't have to be told by you.
I will never let go of that hand.
I'm not in a rush, but I just want an answer.
Well…
No, I…
I'm sorry.
Honestly, I didn't think you would be this surprised.
I thought you would be at least a tad bit happy…
I was wondering what would be a good gift for your 29th birthday, and…
I'm such a fool, I guess I must've gotten everything wrong.
I don't seem to understand you at all, Iwaya.
No, it's not that…
I didn't mean to corner you like that.
I just wanted you to be a little more at ease.
So…
I thought maybe a marriage would be for the best.
I'm sorry…
I didn't mean to make you frown like that.
Oh… no, it's my fault.
No, but you have your own job and everything.
I guess I can't expect you to just suddenly accept marriage and a foreign country.
It's too sudden, isn't it?
Well, for now, let's just forget about this.
No, it's not like that.
Umm, I…
I love…
I love you.
I always have, a lot.
But it was just so sudden right now, and I didn't know how to react.
I'm really happy about your feelings for me.
What should I do…?
I love you too.
So that's enough for me.
I'm not going to rush you.
Senpai.
Wow, we're talking about some very embarrassing stuff really early in the day, huh?
You're right.
Let's go someplace where there's nobody around.
You are my pet
8. The end of moratorium
In a sense, it's ideal…
Getting proposed to by your beloved on your 29th birthday.
But you know, I think senpai thought I would be more excited like, "Oh my gosh, I'd love to get married!"
But I totally let him down.
So what are you going to do now?
I don't know.
I like him, but it's still early for marriage.
You're right, you guys haven't even had sex yet.
Wait.
You're kidding me, you've done it?
You've done it!
Just a litle while ago, finally.
I'm so happy for you!
And? And? And?
How was it?
What do you mean, how was it?
Actually, he was pretty good. His technique was pretty impressive.
That's to be expected, since he's such a good catch.
But you know, honestly…
things like marriage and Rio de Janeiro were going round and round in my head.
Honestly, I wasn't able to concentrate very well.
Oh, what a waste…
But most of all, senpai can just take me to Rio de Janeiro, and work his butt off, but I…
Will lose your career as well as your current life.
Exactly.
But you know, there are women who think of that as happiness.
Yeah…
I can't do this, I don't think I'm mature enough for marriage yet.
What are you saying at the age of 29?
Let me tell you this…
It's not that you're not mature enough, it's just that you don't want to become mature.
That's not true, it's been seven years since I left my parents' house.
Financial independence and psychological independence are different.
You are still stuck in a sea of moratorium.
Moratorium?
I'm home!
Yup, with him.
Sumire-chan, sorry I was late!
Wait a minute. Let go of me, Momo!
The shampoo doesn't smell like ours.
What?! Just don't stick to me like that!
That's because it's the smell of the shampoo at Hasumi-san's.
Yuri-chan, don't talk about that in front of the pet…
You're joking! Even though it was a daytime date?
On top of that, it was the memorable first time!
Really?! You hadn't done it with him yet?
Well, there were apparently a few attempts until now…
Wow, and on your birthday too!
I can see Hasumi-kun liking that kind of a sappy situation.
I know! And in the day, even though he has night duty!
Hey, you two… stop making a conversation over people's sex lives!
I wonder if I have another bottle of wine…
What?
You're not hurt by this… are you?
No way.
If I were to get hurt by a little thing like my master having sex, being a pet would be a tough job.
What a tough job…
But to be asked for relationship advice at this late hour is rather unpleasant.
Please forgive me. Today is my birthday.
I see… then it can't be helped.
Then I'll only listen to you for three minutes.
Iwaya-san, are you having a difficult time deciding on marriage?
Yes, that's the problem.
And why is that?
I don't know myself…
Are you dissatisfied with him at all?
No.
Is there another man who interests you?
The sex isn't all that great.
No!
Excuse me…
I just don't think I have the will to throw away my current lifestyle, my career,
my house, my last name, nor my pet all at once.
I just feel that women have to sacrifice more than men for the sake of marriage.
I don't feel dissatisfaction with him at all.
But you think you'll feel cramped when it comes to spending the rest of your lives together.
Yeah, maybe there's a little bit of that.
Makes sense.
I see.
Then maybe it's too early for you to marry.
But it'll be so hard to be so far away from senpai.
And starting todat, I'm already 29, and I feel bad sending him overseas on his own.
But it's not possible to choose both.
If I was a little younger, I could get married just for the feeling of love.
But now…
But now, I want to stay like this a little longer…
Moratorium doesn't last forever.
You're out of time.
Well then, happy birthday to you ~
Hey, wait…
She can't just keep running away.
Sumire-chan, the bathtub's free.
Are you serious?! Did you empty the entire bottle while I was taking a bath?
Sumire-chan, you'll catch a cold.
Sumire-chan, are you okay?
How defenseless you look.
Let's get you to bed.
C'mon, wake up! Come on!
Hey, Sumire! I'll check out your panties!
I'll charge 100 yen if you do…
100 yen? Isn't that a little too cheap?
You have to value yourself more.
Geez, give me a break.
She's so heavy…
Hey!
Oh, Nishida-san!
Sorry, sorry… I didn't mean to surprise you like that.
Hey, isn't this Goda Takeshi?
You know him?
Sure I do.
Anyone who has an interest in dance should know him.
Is this your article?
No, no… I've just met him before, that's all.
Can you introduce him to me then?
I don't know his address. He seems to have run away from home.
What?
I heard he's going to have a performance soon at "Forest Hall 21".
I've been keeping an eye on him even before I had entered the Culture department.
Momo?
Huh? Why am I in bed? Huh? Pajamas…
Don't worry, I didn't take off your bra and panties.
What?! Why—
Oh, my head hurts…
Here's water.
Thanks.
Here's some medicine.
I don't feel so good.
Here's a barf bag. I'll put it behind you.
What time is it now?
2:30 AM. Your birthday's over.
This sucks, to drink too much and be sick on my birthday.
Don't worry about it, it can be just another memory for you.
A memory?
Yeah.
You know, I'll stay around until you tell me to get out.
Always?
Always.
Even if it's decades?
Yup, even decades.
Even if I become a grandma?
Yeah, even if you become a grandma, Sumire-chan.
Hey, is it true that you've decided to not go to Germany?
Yup, I decided not to.
Are you serious? I can't believe you.
Germany's so hard!
You're lying. It's because of that woman, isn't it?
Yes, but is that anything to you?
Why?
It's not like she's your girlfriend, right?
You're just a pet to her.
Whoa, what's that?!
You're kidding me. What happened, Junpei?
Nothing… I just came back from job interviews.
It looks great on you, Junpei!
Yeah, it's not bad at all.
Actually, I think I'm going to be able to get into a 2-year university too.
Oh? That's going to work out for you? That's awesome!
Everyone's changing so quickly.
Is it really okay that you stay like that forever?
And, he said that he wasn't in a rush, but he wanted an answer!
Are you serious?! A real proposal?!
Ohno-san from the Society department saw Hasumi-san giving her the ring at a restaurant!
Then it's coming up!
Isn't that a shock?! You were such a fan of Hasumi-san's.
Not really. I was just a little disappointed.
Besides, right now I'm doing pretty well with a young dealer of foreign cars.
Oh, really?
So do you think they're going to have the wedding ceremony and then fly over there?
Umm, Iwaya-san?
Yes?
You're not going to quit your job, are you?
I heard a rumor that you were going to get married and go to Rio de Janeiro.
How did it get out so soon? No, I'm not really…
If you're going to quit just for marriage, then you shouldn't start working in the first place.
What's that supposed to mean?
But it can't really be helped if they're going overseas.
That's why I don't like women.
When you think they finally adapted to their jobs, they quit so easily.
But you know… it hasn't been decided yet, right?
Umm… I haven't said anything about quitting…
All right, let's go to lunch! Let's go.
Yes.
What the heck was that?
Iwaya-san, I'm done with the calculations.
Thank you.
But wow, you have some nerve to have a pet.
I just thought it was a normal case of double-dealing.
I haven't done such a thing!
But it's the same to a man.
Then would you be fine with Hasumi-san having a woman pet at his house?
Well…
Which are you going to choose?
If you're unsure, then why don't you just give Hasumi-san to me?
You're really serious about Hasumi-kun.
You're kidding, right? Why would I do something inefficient like truly falling for someone?
Choose one or… the other?
Takeshi-san! Actually, you know…
You're still living here?
There's been an unforeseen happening.
Unforeseen? What's that have to do with me?
Takeshi.
Mom.
Why?
Why don't you sit down, instead of just standing there?
Or would you like to invite me up to your home?
Hey, you guys…
Wa-wait… please don't bother them.
I've seen them before, but exactly who are they and what floor do they live on?
They're my wife and son.
You're kidding me!
Yes, I am.
It's a lie that I've always wanted to say.
Oh, really.
I'm very sorry.
I see.
You came to see me for something?
My, my…
What?
You've become so handsome.
It pisses me off.
You were so cute back in the day.
Don't say things that are hard for me to respond to.
What's that scarf for?
It's not a scarf, leave it alone.
You've grown taller, haven't you?
Well, I suppose I'm taller than I was four years ago.
The spring when you were 16 years old, when you ran away from home, you were still only 166 cm.
I think he's grown another 3 cm.
Shut up.
Keep your mouth shut.
Go elsewhere.
Yes.
So you're owned by a woman here?
Go to Germany.
What?
I've just turned in your application for you.
You're joking!
I don't have the time to waste making jokes.
I took the time to cancel my lessons and come out to Tokyo.
Why don't you show some more gratitude?
But this has nothing to do with you!
What do you mean, nothing to do with me?
I'm an adult now, I can do things by myself.
Don't act so haughty towards me when you're living like this.
You thought that I didn't feel anything after you didn't call once for four years?
Do you think I didn't worry?
I thought that maybe you'd come home for your 20th birthday.
I baked some flan and waited for you.
How should I know about that?
I don't regret leaving home.
Stop!
Don't talk.
I feel like crying.
I'm going home.
You're going home?
I have lessons tonight.
My students are waiting for me.
I'm not going to Germany.
I'm not going home either.
I've finally found my place.
I have to choose between Momo or Hasumi-senpai?
But if I choose one, I'll surely lose the other.
Hey, are you going to do your toenails? Let me do it.
Fine, but don't mess it up.
I know.
For your date tonight.
Dang, your pinky toe is small!
It would be scary if it were big! Stop it, that tickles!
Then is this okay?
Don't touch me like that!
Then how should I touch you?
Firmly.
Is this okay?
Don't move, I'm going to concentrate.
Your face looks so serious.
I am serious! Let me focus!
Ah… you made me mess up!
Really, don't move.
All right.
Hey, your performance is this coming Saturday, right?
Yup.
It's been a long time since I've seen you dance.
It's based on Greek mythology. I save a princess that's about to get eaten by a monster.
Wow, I'm envious.
Of what?
You get kind of envious of the princesses from back in the day.
They feel happy just by being swept away by a prince.
Women of today are too complicated.
If it were you, I'd go save you.
Whenever, wherever you may be.
I'm not so weak as to be saved by a pet. I can knock down a monster with my aikidou.
Yeah, I know.
But don't you think that one person and a pet is a lot better than just one person alone?
Oops, I messed up again.
After this dries,
it's nice outside, so we can go for a walk.
Huh?
Yay! Yay!
This is the first time in a while that we've taken a walk!
Come to think of it, that's true.
I feel kind of happy.
What?
Stop it, don't hold my hand!
But we're taking a walk, right? This makes up for the leash.
Wait, people will wonder what kind of a relationship we're in.
What kind? Well you're the master, and I'm the pet…
Don't say it!
Society isn't so nice as to just accept reality as it is.
But you're the one who told me to become a pet!
Man, this is boring!
Wait, Momo!
Let's eat.
Wow, it looks good!
Wait! Wipe your hands first!
Okay.
Now you can eat.
All right! Itadakimasu~
Mmm… It's good!
Do you want some sausage too?
Here you go, catch!
One more, one more!
Here!
Nice catch!
Here's another one!
I've trained you well!
Sumire-chan, tea!
Here.
Hurry, hurry!
There, there…
You're really like a dog.
Today is so nice.
It would have been nice if I really were a dog.
Then, even if you got married, we could still always be together.
Huh?
This quail looks like a chick.
How did you know that?
I've told you, I can read what you're thinking.
This quail is cute.
Do you want to eat it, Sumire-chan?
No, it's okay.
Then I'll eat it.
There we go.
Then don't marry him.
What?
Because I'll always be by your side.
That's not right.
It's wrong to stay like this forever.
Momo, you can't stay a pet forever either, right?
Yeah, I guess.
Oh, today feels so good!
I kind of wish that time would just stop like this.
If only time would stop like this.
This moment may be
the most comfortable time for me in my life.
I could lock this moment
in my memory for the rest of my life.
Momo…
You're right.
The sun is going to set soon.
Let's finish our lunch.
Yeah.
Itadakimasu.
Hey, stop it!
Wait a minute! What do you mean?!
That hurts!
Hey! What's going on?!
How dare you!
Give me back my money!
Stop!
What's going on here?
Hey!
Where is it?
What are you doing to her?
Who the hell are you?
I'm an acquaintance of hers.
Oh, so you got tricked by her too?
What?
Are you stupid? You're the one that got tricked on your own.
Who in their right mind would seriously go out with you?
What'd you say?!
Stop it! Violence is not the solution!
Get out of the way, punk!
Oh, I'm sorry…
It hurts…
Oh, but he's…
It doesn't matter, hurry!
I wonder if senpai's late…
Are you okay?
Why… why did you save me?
What do you mean, why?
You should know by now that I'm that kind of a woman.
I just catch rich guys and fling them around and do what I want!
Even with you, Hasumi-san…
Be careful when you go home. I'll see you at work.
Wait!
Don't go.
I… I like you, Hasumi-san.
I like you so much, I can't help it.
Even if you don't like me, I'll do anything. Please…
It can be just once…
Make love to me.
I don't think you should say something like that.
All right?
Heh… you should just take advantage of me.
What a boring man.
What?
If you're too good of a person, you'll be made a fool of. Like with Iwaya-san…
Iwaya?
It must be some kind of mistake.
Like she must have flung herself on him.
Or maybe he was caring for someone that looks like Fukushima-san that collapsed.
Or maybe it was a worker that looked just like senpai
that was putting away a dummy that looked exactly like Fukushima-san.
As if that could be.
Maybe I should go home…
Iwaya!
Senpai…
I'm sorry, I got involved in a fight over there.
A fight?
Yes, I'm sorry.
I made you wait 15 minutes!
Oh no, not at all.
I'm glad you waited though.
Why can't I ask him?
Why can't I ask, "You were with Fukushima-san just now, weren't you?"
All right.
I don't want to be seen as a troublesome woman.
I don't want to be thought of as jealous.
I want to always be cool. I don't want him to dislike me.
I want to stay the cute woman that knows nothing, and look like nothing ever bothers me.
Oh… I have a headache.
What he sees of me, is actually not myself.
I see.
He told me he likes how I have a good hold of myself,
and how I'm gentle and share the same values as him.
But the actual me is easily affected, pitiful, and pretty deceptive.
My personality's bad, and I get jealous easily.
And it's just that I try my best to match my preferences and values to him.
Wait, wait…
Self-respect, pride.
Self-absorption, narcissism.
This is very imbalance for you.
Your pride is much larger.
To put it simply, you are too scared to put your true self out there,
and you try to become the person that people expect you to be.
You can only show the part of you that doesn't show any weaknesses and is flawless.
This lack of balance is what continually bothers and pricks at your heart.
And currently, Momo-chan is in the role of freeing you to go towards narcissism.
I was also like this.
That's why I brought my dog into my marriage.
But it proved to be a failure.
I could only show my true self to my dog, and I caused my wife great stress.
So that's how it was…
This is the child of that dog.
In order for me not to overly love my dog, I've been careful to call it a different name every day.
What is that dog's real name?
Fusae.
Fusae?
It's my previous wife's name.
To your right.
The performance has started, so please take your seats immediately.
Sensei, your ticket… sensei… your ticket!
Hey, isn't that Goda Yoshie?
Wow, you're kidding me!
Mom…
Mom, everyone's watching.
You really do piss me off.
How hard you must have worked while I wasn't around to watch you.
Takeshi, you still don't understand your talent.
You can still fly so much higher.
How long are you going to keep running away from it?
Speak for yourself, you should've just broken up with Dad by now.
That's none of your business.
Well, it's all right…
Wherever you fly off to, you are my son that'll always make me proud.
Mom.
I love my life.
I'm grateful to you too.
So saucy.
I wonder when Momo's going to come out.
Goda-san's coming!
Mo—
Not Momo, umm…
Sumire-chan!
Momo?
Yeah?
Great job.
You looked really cool.
Of course.
I worked hard so I could get this.
Whatever you say…
Thanks.
Today is omelette one rice, okay?
Darn it, how did I let him do that to me?
Oh, Iwaya-san?
Senpai…
Excuse me.
Hey, wait!
Senpai!
Senpai, will you wait a moment?
What was that back there?
Him…
What kind of a relationship are you two in?
Oh…
Umm…
He is…
I…
Sorry, Hasumi-kun!
I'm really sorry.
Actually, to tell the truth, I like Sumire-chan.
I liked her for the longest time. I really admired her.
So today, I kind of forced her, asking her to come see me with a huge bouquet of flowers.
I'm actually going to Germany next week.
Germany?
Yeah, I'm going abroad to study in Frankfurt.
There's a pretty big contemporary dance group over there.
I'm going to go there, and my dream is to become a great, world-famous international dancer.
But then I won't be able to see Sumire-chan anymore.
So to mark my final goodbye, I stole a kiss from her.
Sorry, Sumire-chan.
You proposed to her, right?
I heard from my older sister that Sumire-chan got a gorgeous ring from you.
I wish you two happiness from a far away sky.
Bye.
I'm sorry.
I misjudged you.
It's not like that.
He…
He is my…
Hey, Iwaya-san!
What a coincidence.
The landlord…
Actually we got tickets from one of our residents. Are you two on a date?
No, I just got off work.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Where's the omelette rice you promised?
Just give me a minute.
Thanks for the bouquet.
It made me really happy.
No, I have to thank you for lying for me like that.
I was so surprised.
You're so good at lying, Momo.
Things like Germany and studying abroad, you tell lies that sound like the truth.
Even I almost thought they were true…
They're true.
Huh?
Sorry… it's true that I'm going abroad.
What?
I'm going to Germany next week.
I was planning on it from the start.
I was wondering when I should tell you,
but I guess I just couldn't find the right timing.
You're joking, what are you talking about?
It's not a joke.
So…
Let's have a good time for the remaining week…
Master.