Momo…
Dad and Mom were fighting again.
Momo, I love you.
This is the pet I used to own as a child…
Momo.
Hey, could you wash properly behind my ears too?
It's because you're moving too much.
Don't splash so much… Momo!
More towards the front.
Huh… where?
There, there.
Oh, that feels good~
And this is the pet "Momo" I now own.
It was on a rainy day two weeks ago.
[sign]Two weeks ago
Let me see…
the last time I cried was when I was in middle school.
It was when my pet died after getting sick.
Since then, I've never cried again.
Oh, and when I broke a bone during Aikidou,
I felt the tears coming, but I didn't cry.
Lately I don't even laugh much because I've been too busy with work.
That's not very healthy.
My coworkers call me names like cyborg,
Noh-men and kokeshi doll behind my back.
But you're so beautiful.
No…
I got dumped by a man.
He said that I lacked a sense of peace.
He says he feels inferior when he's with me.
Well, I graduated from Tokyo University and have experience studying abroad at Harvard.
He was lower than me in income, educational background, even in height.
But the one who cheated was not I, but him.
I'm sick of men and their inferiority complexes.
Not that I still feel any attachment, nor am I hurt.
But I can't sleep.
My head has been hurting for ten days now.
I see…
I understand.
This is my first time coming to a place like this so I don't know much,
but do you prescribe medication? Like a tranquilizer?
Well, let's try to smile.
Huh?
Let me see you smile.
I see… it is true. You do lack a sense of peace.
Today's people are dry.
And a smile is like a drop of water falling onto their dry hearts.
A beautiful drop of water… don't you think so?
No. I don't quite understand what you're trying to say.
No matter how beautiful and successful you are,
if you are not able to offer that water to people, as a person, you are the worst.
The worst?
Even a kokeshi doll could be considered cuter.
Thank you very much, that'll be enough.
Forgive me, I have not yet made my diagnosis.
No, thank you.
I was the stupid one for coming to counseling just for a slight headache.
Did you love him?
That man who was lower than you in height and income.
I have just the cure for you.
Try crying…
as much as you can.
No, I'd rather die than cry in front of other people.
Next patient, please.
You're lucky… you're pretty and smart…
Honestly speaking, it's easier for me to be with her.
Kuraki-san, where are the papers that I asked for?
I'm sorry, I'll prepare them right away,
If you start preparing them now, how much time will it take?
Oh, umm… about an hour and a half.
Didn't I tell you absolutely by 2 o'clock?
Nevermind… I'll prepare them myself.
I'm so sorry.
It's all right.
It's my fault for asking you.
I see Iwaya-san is scary as usual…
It's okay…
I know I'm not as smart as Iwaya-san…
Are you crying?
Don't cry, you poor thing…
I'm telling you, don't cry.
Don't cry.
Iwaya-san… don't cause trouble.
Don't behave like that when the government officials visit.
My behavior?
I just greeted them as I normally would.
What I'm saying is…
Just because they touched your back a little, you don't have to get out of your seat like that.
Excuse me, but they didn't touch my back, they touched my rear.
Oh, really?
Only Official Suzuki would have the guts to touch the butt of a fearsome woman like you.
Normal men would be too scared to do that sort of thing.
Don't look so scary.
Would you like me to touch it too?
Shoot…
It's not like me to be angered by something trivial like this.
What's wrong with me?
What am I going to do?
It'll either be a salary reduction or expulsion for improper behavior.
Trash?
Is he dead…?
What should I do… go to the police?
No, ambulance…
Raining?
What am I going to do?
Oh… excuse me…
Umm… excuse me…
Oh, good evening…
What is this? This box?
Oh… this actually isn't my stuff.
I told you[,] trash in bulk must be reported.
No, this is different… I just found and picked it up just now.
Picked up? So it's an animal?
I told you pets are not allowed in this appartment complex.
No, it's not.
Let me look inside. Is it a doggy or a kitty?
No!
It's even more suspicious that you try to hide it.
I will have to inspect that!
I'm telling you, it's not.
Iwaya-san,
Excuse me.
Iwaya-san!
I guess first off, I should notify the police…
He's like a dog…
Wow… 39 degrees.
It tastes good…
The next morning, as the rain cleared,
the headache that had lasted ten days had also disappeared.
Oh… oh man, the report!
[sign]Kimi wa petto
You are my pet
[sign]1. How to care for a beautiful boy
Shibusawa Rumi?
You know Goda Takeshi, correct?
Of course you know him…
he's your boyfriend.
What's this old man talking about?
I want to know his whereabouts.
If I knew, I would go see him myself, stupid!
Leave her alone, Rumi and Takeshi just broke up!
Don't say insensitive things to her, you old man.
Excuse me,
this man just asked us for prostitution.
Stupid Takeshi…
Please eat the soft rice.
Even if you have no appetite, I think you should eat.
I will take the key with me, so you can go home whenever you want.
What? You let a boy sleep at your house?
Yeah, it's just how things ended up in the course of events.
Sumire, even someone like you has to be careful about that kind of things.
What do you mean, a person like me?
I'm just saying, even with a strong person like you,
it could be dangerous to let a young man into the house so easily.
It's okay!
He has a delicate build. Plus, his arm was injured.
Injured? That seems even more suspicious.
He could be involved with something dangerous, like the yakuza.
That's hard to believe…
As soon as he wakes up, I'm sure he'll just obediently go home.
You make it sound like he's a stray cat.
Yes, that's it, Yuri-chan.
What?
He reminds me of Momo.
Momo?
Wasn't Momo the dog you used to own back in middle school?
Yeah. So I felt like I couldn't just leave him there.
Are you stupid?
Iwaya-kun.
Oh, chief. I'm really sorry about yester—
[sign]Official announcement:
[sign]Iwaya Sumire of the External Affairs department will be transferred to the Lifestyle department.
Look, Iwaya-san from External Affairs is being moved to Lifestyle.
What? From External Affairs to Lifestyle?
That sucks, she was such an elite.
I heard she punched out the External Affairs chief and knocked out his front tooth.
Scary.
Yeah, and she just got called to the Head Chief's office…
Sorry, I'll call you later.
Long time, no see.
Thank you very much. Please come again.
Here is your ashtray.
Thank you.
Please enjoy.
This is your spare key.
You could've just thrown it away.
Sorry, were you busy now?
Not particularly. How is your girlfriend?
Her baby's due next month, right?
How are you?
What do you mean?
Huh? Uhh… I mean…
how are you lately?
I'm fine.
Does it look like I've been spending my days crying?
But… you got transferred to the Lifestyle department, right?
I heard you had some trouble with your department chief,
so I was kind of worried…
He just broke his front tooth. In any case, it has nothing to do with you.
You don't have to talk like that.
It's pretty hard on you, isn't it?
Because I know that deep down, you're a very timid and thoughtful person.
I'm sorry I can't support you in a time like this, but…
Just because we went out for a mere two and a half years, don't act like you know everything.
Oh, I'll pay.
Don't worry about it.
But don't expect any gift from me when your baby's born.
Your check?
Thank you very much.
There's nothing a woman can gain from being strong.
Excuse me?
Sometimes I envy you.
Thank you very much.
That was Iwaya-san's ex-boyfriend that just came, wasn't it?
Oh, that guy from the Printing department.
I guess they broke up after all.
Well, I saw it coming.
Who would really feel comfortable with a woman
higher than you in educational background, salary, and even height?
Shh!! She'll hear you.
Oh, welcome home!
Why are you still here?
Oh, I didn't have any money to ride the train.
Thanks for the food.
It was de~licious!
Really? I'm happy to see you're feeling better.
Yeah, thanks to you, I'm feeling great!
Then please go home.
Or perhaps I should notify the police?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I just drank some water a while ago.
That's fine, it's just water.
But I was lucky to be found by a good person like you.
When I catch a cold before spring, it ends up becoming asthma.
Found? Are you some kind of stray dog?
Yeah, close. I don't have a place to live right now.
Lately, I've been staying here and there.
Last night a hotel owner suddenly attacked me—
Attacked you?
Yeah!
I thought I was lucky he was letting me stay for free,
but then he told me to pay him back with my body.
But I couldn't bring myself to do that,
so I ran away as fast as I could, but the guys who were chasing me were so persistent.
I was hiding in that box, and before I knew it, I fell asleep.
I don't quite understand what you're trying to say.
Until now, I've met all kinds of nice people,
but this is the first time I've met someone as kind as you.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I helped you yesterday because I felt I had to,
but I normally don't let strange men into my house.
If you're that healthy, get out now.
I'll give you money for the train.
I don't feel so good.
Just a moment ago, you told me you were feeling great! Where's your home?
Oh yeah, I want to eat some curry—
I didn't ask you to decide the dinner menu!
I'm asking you where you live!
Umm…
here?
I want to live here.
Please! Can you let me stay here for a while?
Ouch!!
Let go!
I won't ask you to make me your boyfriend.
Do you have a boyfriend?
None of your business! I'm not interested in younger men anyway.
Is that so?
Whether I like younger men or not isn't your business either.
Lady, you're an interesting person.
You're good at cooking, and I think we'd get along great.
Ha! I'm a cold hard-core career woman. Not an interesting person at all!
This morning, when I woke up, I felt sooo happy.
There was food, and blankets, and your sweet smell.
Don't smell me!
I felt that I wanted to stay here together with you.
If you keep talking nonsense, I'll call the police!
Phew… If that gossipy landlord saw such a scene,
who knows what he would say.
That's a relief.
It's no use looking at me with those puppy dog eyes.
Then anything, I'll do anything.
I'll play your younger brother, or I can be your playmate.
I'll be your bodyguard, or a gangster, or even a masseur.
Anything?
Anything.
Don't you have any kind of pride?
No, I don't.
I'm not interested in K-1 anymore either.
[note]K-1 is professional wrestling championship
I dunno, something about professional wrestling… the muscles…
Then why don't you become my pet?
I could let you stay here as a pet.
Pet?
Yes, a pet.
If you're good, I'll take care of you and cook for you.
But you won't have any rights, and you'll have to obey everything I say.
How about it?
I don't get any rights?
No, because you'd be a pet.
Are you serious?
Yes. You can't comply, can you?
Then please leave immediately.
Ruff!
Wan?
Okay, I'll become your pet. Man, that's it? How lucky!
Wait, do you know what this means? By pet…
Yes, Master.
Making a boy a pet is not normal.
This is good. It's really delicious!
It's not human, it's not common sense.
Are you…
a person who talks a lot to yourself?
There's a lot of housewives like that,
who mumble to themselves about their husbands' coming home late, and single women…
Okay, I'm going to ask you one more time—
I'll become your pet.
By the way, you've asked that question for the 14th time.
You can't take it back now and say you won't take care of me anymore.
I don't want to be sent off to the shelter.
Thank you for the food! I'm grateful again to my master.
I don't have any intention of sleeping with you.
What are you surprised about? Of course I wouldn't!
Just because I let you live here with me, I don't want you to get such loose ideas.
I wanted to be by myself for a while anyway.
I didn't feel like living with a man for a while, and now I'm not even interested in men.
I'm sick of their selfishness.
I feel inferior…
when I'm with you.
Just because they're not as successful as a woman they feel tormented.
Seems so stupid…
he is stupid and I'm stupid too.
Even though I graduated from Tokyo University, I went out with that kink of a guy for two and a half years.
Oh well, enough about that. What I'm trying to say is…
Don't sleep!
Oh, sorry.
I felt full and before I knew it…
Are you a really weird person?
Oh yeah, come to think of it, my friends often tell me, "You're really weird."
My girlfriend always called me "stupid".
Well, I already broke up with her though.
That's good, I think it was right to break up with her.
But as a pet, I think I'd do well.
Listen to what a person is saying.
What are you doing?
The pose of submission.
I submit to you.
If you say no sex, then I won't do anything inappropriate.
If you say you want me to, then I can do that for you too.
And I won't.
And your pet can even do acts like this.
That's pretty good.
Right?
Yeah, I kind of feel like rewarding you with food.
Right? Right?
I won't disobey you, and I will do anything to make my master happy.
And I wouldn't do anything to hurt you, ever.
Is your arm okay?
Yup, thanks to my master's care.
Oh and, just to let you know…
I love them — K-1, pride, and professional wrestling.
If you're serious about living here, don't forget it.
Gotcha!
Awesome!
That's all empty so you can use it freely.
Really?
After 12, use the bath quietly,
because the landlord will get annoyed if he gets complaints from the neighbors.
Oh hey, can I have this?
Yeah, you can have it. I bought it and never used it.
This is my bedroom, so make sure you don't enter it. And over there is the bathroom.
Be absolutely sure to use it cleanly.
Hey, why is this apartment so big when you only live by yourself?
Because I bought it with plans of getting married.
What? You're getting married?!
No, I'm not.
The man got pregnant the girl he was cheating with and left.
Oh…
sorry.
It's all right, I don't care.
I see.
Oh man, forgot something important.
What is it?
Your name. I haven't asked it yet.
Oh, I'm Iwaya.
I know that, it's on your front door. I meant your first name.
Iwaya Sumire.
Sumire?
I see, Sumire-chan.
Sumire-san,
Sumire-chan,
Sumire-kun,
Yo Sumire!
Hey, hey!
SUMIRE!
Yes?
Can you not repeat it like that? I don't like that name.
Then what do people call you?
"Iwaya-san.'
Even your ex?
Yes, is there something wrong with that?
You don't have any nicknames?
I don't want to tell you.
Then I'll just call you Sumire-chan.
You should let people call you that, it's such a pretty name.
What about you?
Me?
I am…
Why don't you give me one? You can give me whatever name you like.
Because I'm your pet, that's how things work, isn't it?
That's true.
Anything is fine, your favorite celebrity's name,
or the name of your first love, maybe the guy you lost your virginity to.
Then Momo.
Momo? Was he a foreigner?
It's the name of the dog I used to own.
A dog?!
The way your hair curls looks just like him.
Plus, that name is for a female dog.
You told me I could give you whatever name I wanted.
What are you doing?
Just wait a sec.
There.
Here. You wouldn't want to use mine by accident, would you?
True.
I see…
so I'm Momo from now on.
Takeshi?
Oh, Takeshi hasn't been coming recently.
He was a kind of free wanderer in the first place so he doesn't really show up often.
Hey, are you part of the paparazzi? Or maybe a fan of his?
There's a lot of them lately…
male fans.
Uh, no, it's not really like that.
But I don't think you have a chance…
he's straight.
Although he's cute.
It's a shame.
Is something wrong, Junpei?
Oh, I was just wondering what Takeshi's up to.
Huh? Did Takeshi contact you?
What's that supposed to mean?
Takeshi, Takeshi! Why is everyone so interested in him?!
I am Iwaya, recently transferred from the External Affairs department.
I look forward to working with you all.
Okay, gotcha. Your seat is over there.
Thank you.
Perhaps this is…
a very direct prank?
Yes… uhuh… I see…
Oh, I understand.
Yes, that would be very helpful actually.
It's her.
Oh, Iwaya-san. How do you do?
I am Ishida. I got moved to the Lifestyle department this year.
Oh, nice to meet you.
Pleased to meet you.
Umm, the one on the phone is Tsumeyama-san, and—
I know. After all, I work in the same company.
Oh yes, of course. Excuse me.
Hey hey hey. Ishida recently came in, but here, he's an upper official.
Don't have too much pride. That's why I don't like elite women.
Don't have to say—
I apologize. Excuse my rudeness.
Well if you've always walked the path of an elite,
I suppose this place would be more of a demotion for you.
Of course not!
The Lifestyle column is the most widely read and covers the most genres.
That kind of model answer gets on my nerves.
Oh, don't punch me out.
I just fixed up these two front teeth.
It's worse that you're a woman who's intelligent and too strong for her own good.
My head hurts.
What?! Iwaya-san's in the Lifestyle department now?
Yeah, it's kind of unlikely, isn't it?
She's moved up her career at such a fast pace,
going from the branch and into the External Affairs department in just half a year.
I heard she also broke up with Yoshida-san of the Printing department.
They didn't really go together in the first place.
Yeah, I mean, Iwaya-san was even taller than him, right?
I don't know if I should say this, but…
don't you feel like she kind of deserves it?
People who can do anything kind of get on my nerves.
Like, "Who do you think you are?"
Oh, I know what you mean.
Isn't that the reason Yoshida-san broke up with her?
Yeah, I'm sure that's part of it.
Damn it.
Hey, young lady, are you alone?
Is something wrong with being alone? I like being alone.
Don't say sad things like that.
I'm not sad at all.
Being alone is good. I like being alone. So leave me alone!
Thank you.
I'm home.
Welcome home!
Wha— Stop…
Sumire-chan, I was waiting for you, all this time.
I had so many things to talk to you about.
Just a little while ago on TV, they were showing these weird ghost pictures,
and it was really stupid, but I couldn't stop laughing.
Oh, and
it looks like they're gonna show a wrestling match soon. They were showing a commercial for it earlier.
I think it starts at one o'clock? It's good that you got home in time.
Oh! Oh! And you know how there's a planting pot by your window?
Did you know there's a bud coming out?
It's purple, and really tiny, but what kind of flower is it?
What's wrong, Sumire-chan?
Are you happy that I'm home?
What am I saying?
I'm happy.
Really happy.
Because I've been waiting this whole time, since you left this morning,
for you to come home.
I see.
Stroke it.
What?
I waited like a good boy.
Good boy.
What a good boy, Momo.
Oww!
Don't cross the line.
What?
I don't have any pet-kissing fetishes.
Are you serious? I always did it!
Like to my friend's kitty. Muah muah muah muah~
No way, not that.
Recently there have been a lot of cases of infections by pets.
It's not good to indiscriminately kiss or sleep beside your pet.
That's what I read before in the Lifestyle column.
Infection? It's okay, I don't have any diseases.
Well, I do have asthma, but—
And why are you talking to me like that?
Only men who are taller than me and higher in education and income can talk to me like that.
What?! That's ridiculous.
I decided it that way. How tall are you?
169 cm…
I'm 172 cm.
I am higher than you in height, education and income.
If you're a pet, act like one and don't do anything unnecessary.
This sucks.
Mama~
How is the new department?
It's weird.
I don't feel nerve-wracked trying to get in things at the last minute for midnight deadlines,
and I don't have to worry about other papers getting breaking stories first.
Plus, I can have Sundays off.
You finally get some free time, and you don't know what to do with it.
I walk my pet.
Coming all the way to the suburbs like this.
Because if I'm seen by any coworkers, it'll be a mess.
And where is he, that pet?
Aren't those shoes cute? I bought them for him in Shibuya the other day,
although I was a little annoyed that the size was the same as mine.
And what an agile pet he is.
He told me he does modern dance.
He must be young. How old is he?
20 years old.
Really? Are you sure he's not a minor still?
Maybe… It doesn't matter. It's not like I'm gonna keep him for a long time.
Oh really?
I thought you were totally into this new boy pet thing.
Into?
No way. How would I get like that over a pet with no common sense?
Are you sure?
Of course.
And it's kind of irritating.
From morning to night, it's "Sumire-chan, Sumire-chan!"
It's cute that he clings to you like that.
Why don't you guys do it once before you kick him out?
What are you talking about?
Look at him, he's cute. And at a ripe age to eat.
Wait, don't say such things in broad daylight in a park full of children.
It's okay!
It's not okay…
Sumire-chan!
Oh, here he comes…
Who is the old lady?
Who are you calling an old lady?!
Yuri-chan is my childhood friend. We went to middle school and high school together.
Really?
At 23, she got married to her handsome pilot boyfriend,
and now she's a wealthy young wife.
Oh Sumire, you're embarrassing me.
Oh, I thought she was just some lady from the neighborhood.
Yeah, actually, I think you should throw this away immediately.
Yuri-chan… you said he was at a ripe age…
Well, whatever.
Ran, let's get going.
Just a little more.
We can come tomorrow. Say bye to everyone.
Okay.
You're leaving already?
Yeah, my mother-in-law is coming over today.
Being a housewife is a task in itself.
Thanks for listening to me.
I'm glad you weren't as down as I expected you to be.
You should find a new man soon, instead of just some pet.
Thanks.
See you later. Say "bye bye".
Bye bye.
A man?
Nevermind, let's go home. You played enough, didn't you?
Already???
This is our first date!
I told you this is a walk.
Man… oh, then pull me.
Huh? If you're not gonna follow me, I don't mind just throwing you away.
You're kidding! Wait for me, Sumire-chan.
Oh, it moved.
Really?
It's moving.
I wonder if it's kicking?
I dunno, but it's moving.
Hey, about me…
You should've lied and said I was your new boyfriend.
That' was him, right? Your ex-boyfriend.
It has nothing to do with you, does it?
Oh really?
But I thought you were a lot cuter than that girl.
You're pretty and you're good at cooking.
It's good that you broke up with him. He looks like a guy with no sense.
I'm really happy when I'm walking with you.
I feel cool walking with a beautiful person like you.
You're too good for a loser like that guy.
I told you it has nothing to do with you!
What's with you? Don't talk about it.
Sorry, I just wanted to cheer you up.
You think that's cheering me up? You've got to be joking.
I'm not so weak as to have you cheer me up.
That's not true.
Because I know…
that you're actually very gentle and really lonely deep inside.
I was so happy I almost cried when you made me curry, and when you bought me new shoes.
It's just my obligation as your owner.
But but but…
Are you stupid?
What are you trying to say? You're just a pet.
If you're a pet, then shut up and just sit over there.
Don't talk like you know everything.
Just because you've been with me a few days, don't try to delve into me.
Don't bother me anymore.
That kind of hurts.
Be quiet, be quiet! Don't talk anymore, get out!
Just get out, I'll give you money.
Get out, I like being by myself.
Oh really?
Then do as you please.
Hey…
You were in the park earlier, weren't you?
With Iwaya-san…
Oh, you're talking about Sumire-chan?
Momo?
Momo, I'm sorry—
Sorry, this is kind of sudden…
Your cousin was downstairs and let me in.
Over here, Jolly!
I've been looking for you.
Takeshi-san.
Let's go back together. Sensei…
I won't go back.
I'm going to Germany soon.
Germany?
Yes, to Frankfurt.
I'm going to take a test.
So, tell them that I want to be left alone.
Until then, I'll just find some random place to stay.
Well, I'd found a place I could stay for two or three months,
but I think I got a little too comfortable…
I'll just find another place on my own.
What are you doing?
Oh, umm… I think I stepped on some dog poop.
Are you serious?
What do you want?
Oh, don't worry…
I'll go home right away.
It's not much.
I just wanted to let you know that I'm going to be transferred to the Aomori Factory.
I wanted to talk to you about things before I left.
I don't have anything to discuss with you.
You haven't changed.
Really?
I'm more surprised that you would come visit after all this.
I don't need you taking pity on me.
Oh and, just to let you know, that guy isn't my cousin.
He's a pet.
A pet?
Yes, he's my pet.
I started taking care of him after we broke up.
Wait a minute.
By pet, do you mean you're going out with that young man?
That's not it. A pet is a pet. That's all there is.
You've got to be kidding.
I didn't know my cheating was that much of a shock for you.
What?
Is he a host? Is that it?
Because you can pay well, he's been clinging to you, is that how it is?
I can't believe you'd become interested in a guy like that.
Yeah, maybe I got interested.
What do you mean?
It was fun, this one week.
What are you saying? This is no joke.
You should cut him off immediately.
A guy like that who hasn't an ounce of pride…
Oh, and what is pride to you?
I don't know what pride means to you,
but a truly strong person doesn't care about stuff like pride.
You were constantly telling me back then,
"You're lucky… you're pretty and smart… and get lots of salary… you're lucky, lucky…"
Not noticing that I was tired of that, every day…
And after all that, you ran away.
What do you mean, pride?
That boy who has no pride at all is much better than someone who is always envying others.
A lot better than you!
I see.
You took care of that violet all this time…
the nioi-sumire.
I thought you'd throw away everything I'd given you.
I'm glad…
that in the end, I got to hear how you really felt.
When you found out about my cheating,
you didn't lose your composure.
We broke up without a fuss,
so I always wondered in the back of my mind.
So…
so it was good to hear that.
I'll go now.
Take care.
Take care!
Take care…
Goodbye.
I'm home!
No…
You know,
I really liked him.
He was plain and boring
and not cool at all, but…
he was gentle and really treated me like I was valuable.
I really liked him.
I'm sad…
I'm so sad.
It was this moment,
as I watched her beautiful tears, that I thought I would like to stay her pet a little longer.
At least until spring comes to an end.***
At least until spring comes to an end.
That's how I felt.
[sign]In the office
Iwaya-san, Dr. Ogawa's data has come in.
Thank you.
Umm, if you all have time,
why don't we all go see the cherry blossoms together?
Oh no! It's already this late?!
Shoot, I forgot to prepare Momo's meal.
Momo?
I'm sorry, but after I take this to the Imaging Center,
I think I'll just go home for today.
Please leave the papers on my desk.
Thank you for your hard work.
I wonder what's up with her?
Oh, it seems like she recently got a pet.
Oh, is that so?
But something changed about her.
Right? Right? That's what I thought too.
I'm home.
Sumire-chan!
What? Ugh!
The shampoo started stinging on my hand.
That has nothing to do with me.
So please, can you wash my head?
There's no way I'll do such a thing.
Please, wash my hair!
No way!
Please!
That feels good~
I'm telling you, hold still!
Hey, why are you wearing those sunglasses?
Because I don't want to see you naked, it's better with these on.
I don't mind you seeing~ Here, look!
Even if you don't mind, I don't want to.
Oh, they're kind of clouding up…
Huh? Ouch! Your finger went into my eye!
Are you okay?!
There's tears coming… Hurry up and wash it out, hurry!
Wait a minute.
Hurry, quickly!
Come on!
Two weeks since that rainy day,
I'm still living here.
This story was scheduled to run for a month,
but my chief says he wants to extend it to half a year…
Yes, oh, thank you from us as well!
Yes, I'll call you again later on.
Thank you, goodbye.
Why hello.
Kokeshi doll.
From this week on, I have been asked to take control of the counseling room at this company.
I will be on the 14th floor two days a week. Please come visit sometime.
My Mary-chan seems to be interested in you as well.
Wait a second…
I wonder if Sumire-chan will come home early?
Hasumi-senpai?
You're Iwaya, right?
Long time, no see…
It's been about four years, hasn't it?