Momo, over here!
Come over here, Momo!
Momo, come on! Momo!
You slept with him?
Yeah, we slept together on my bed.
Does that mean…
In the past, I would feel hesitant about it.
But once I let it happen, it wasn't that big of a deal anymore.
Oh, my gosh!
Oh, but we just slept. Got our sleep together.
Then what…
You didn't do it?
Of course I didn't!
Then… while you were sleeping,
it wasn't like this?
Nope, not like that.
More like this.
I don't know… but I felt warm, and I slept well.
Whenever I sleep with a man, I always feel kind of crammed.
With Momo, I don't really think about it too much.
You may feel that way, but are you sure the pet doesn't feel anything either?
Sleeping together, as a man…
I don't think so. He was in a deep sleep, and he didn't toss about.
Momo is actually pretty well brought up.
He doesn't spill food and he's clean when he uses the bathroom.
Maybe because he was a ballerina.
No, maybe that pet doesn't have any interest in women.
I don't think it's like that. He had a girlfriend and stuff.
A girlfriend?
Yup.
I'm asking, are you Takeshi's girl?
Hey, Rumi…
It's okay. It's over between me and him.
Isn't that kind of insolent? For him to have a girlfriend and all.
Umm… I think it's pretty natural, considering he's a male.
And she's actually kind of pretty, too.
You're the one who's abnormal.
Abnormal? Me?
Sleeping with your pet before sleeping with your boyfriend.
Those are two different types of sleeping.
Hasumi-senpai probably thinks it's strange, too.
You come home early from your dates saying, "I have to take care of my pet."
Because he's also pretty busy with work.
And you don't invite him over to your house.
Sleeping together aside… up till this point, you've only let him kiss you.
Well, that's because…
I knew it, I think you're…
Hmm… What?
Actually, I won't say it.
I'm scared if I say it, it'll come true.
What's that supposed to mean?
Despite how this looks, I am a journalist from a major newspaper publisher.
About the project on medicine from the last time,
it won the Bureau Chief Award. So here is the report.
Congratulations!
Wow, I can't believe it. Awesome!
Thank you.
They want to take a picture of you, so make sure you contact the Business Information center.
Understood.
We did it, Iwaya-san!
This is the first time in the last two years, that our department has received the Bureau Chief Award.
Elites are amazing, aren't they?
Stop standing there in admiration. Try harder, you men…
This is my first time, you know… getting the Bureau Chief Award.
Come to think of it… this is my first time as well.
Two months ago,
I was transferred from the External Affairs department to the Lifestyle department,
and I'm just starting to get used to the work here.
Yes. I am a cool, hardcore career woman.
Iwaya.
This is my boyfriend, Hasumi-senpai.
He's tall, has a high educational background and a high income.
What they used to call, the "Top 3", back in those days.
On top of that, he's sweet and hardworking…
and a good kisser.
Are you free tonight?
Sure, if it's around nine.
Then I'll see you later.
Yes.
And the reason I can be this happy is…
I'm home.
Welcome back!
Momo, the pet I've had for two months now.
Ouch! Will you stop jumping on me like that?
I will not stop.
I'm telling you, it hurts!
Hey, hey! Do you have any souvenirs for me?
What! You didn't bring back any?!
I knew it.
There! That's it, OK!
Whoa! He's bleeding!
No!
You're too noisy!
I'm 29 soon…
I know very well that I can't live like this forever.
But…
For now, I don't want to lose these happy moments.
[sign]Kimi wa petto
You are my pet
[sign]6. The night my dog bit me
Thank you for your hard work.
Next week, some of the departments are getting together for a zengen. Did you all know?
A zengen? What's that?
To put it simply, an employee vacation.
It's a term that's used within the newspaper industry.
We're with External Affairs, aren't we?
I'll pass.
Are you kidding? External Affairs?
Don't say that, chief. Let's all go together.
I don't want to. I don't like the guys from External Affairs, nor those from the Society department.
I can't stand them. I just can't get used to them.
Are you going, Iwaya-san?
What? I don't think I will. I've never gone before, why go now?
What's this?!
Oh…
[sign]To my comrade, Iwaya-san
A performance?
Yes, it's set in a motif of a Greek myth.
I really wanted you to be in it… I wanted you to play the brave youth, Perseus.
Sounds interesting. I'll keep it in mind.
I'm glad. Oh yes, is it true that you haven't applied?
To the school in Germany.
Oh…
Come to think of it, it totally slipped my mind.
Get a hold of yourself!
What if you end up not being able to go to Frankfurt?!
It's not a privilige that everyone gets to have.
That's true.
Birdie, you're so cute.
Oh? You're here again, Takeshi.
Lately, he's been coming here every day.
I need you to get a grip on yourself, too. You're the ace of our dance company.
Yes.
Oh, about our upcoming performance…
If Takeshi can't make it, I'm thinking of assigning you the main role, so please do your best.
Right, gotcha.
I like you… a lot.
What?
Wait, wait, wait… stop, Junpei.
Do you mean it?
Yeah, I do.
Then how come during this whole time we've been together, you never made a single move on me?
Because I'm not that much of a masochist.
Huh? Wa… wait a second!
I don't understand what you mean!
Hey, Junpei! Good morning.
I can't always be filling in for you, you know.
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Umm…
I had my heart broken.
What?
Is that so…?
Yes.
That must have been difficult…
Are you all right?
No, it's over for me.
But why…?
Excuse me.
Here is your coffee.
If you'll excuse me.
What?! Don't tell me it's her?
You're kidding me, right? Why such a young girl?
This is your fault.
Excuse me?
It's because you kept seeking advice from me.
This has nothing to do with me… Besides, you're a doctor, aren't you?
Emily-chan, come over here.
You are the only oasis of my heart.
There, there…
What does he expect me to do?!
I know…
Excuse me?
That you and the doctor can only love pets.
What? No, I'm different…
But even so, that doctor…
But, well… how do I say this…
It is kind of a nuisance to have someone in love with you at your workplace…
It's not the love that is a nuisance!
I couldn't stand the fact that he wasn't treating me like a human.
He only feels love for creatures that are weaker than him.
He wants to protect them, he wants them to always be by his side.
But that feeling only comes from feeling superior.
Basically, the perspective of normal humans towards love is just of a different quality.
I may be soft, but I'm not a pet. That is all.
A breakdown?
It's true that all men love big breasts.
Excuse me?
But that's not due to preference. It's because they don't have them.
The reason he is attracted to you
is that his milled heart is unconditionally drawn to your softness.
It's not a feeling of superiority. Well, there may be a little of that.
But to desire something that you lack, I think it's okay to call that love.
Seeing you from the perspective of even a woman like me, you are excellent and graceful.
You're very charming.
I'm sorry. I said too much.
Thank you very much.
Why am I making such a passionate speech?
Did you hear? For the zengen, we're with the Lifestyle department too.
Huh? Oh… Yes.
This year, with the war and election for the House of Councilors, many departments cancelled.
There's a possibility of a breakup election as well,
so the Main department probably can't go either.
I guess those who can should just go.
Yes…
It's been a while since I've been on a vacation to Hakone.
I wonder why they want to go that far…?
Huh?
Iwaya, you don't mean…
Oh… well, I've never been there either…
Really?
I guess…
employee vacations are pretty boring actually.
Yeah… how boring… hot springs and such.
So boring… to have a barbeque with everyone.
It's boring to have a drink with Iwaya in her yukata…
Oh, but…
I was thinking… if it was with External Affairs this year, I may go…
Really?
Yes.
What?
An employee vacation?
Yeah.
That means staying over?
It's only for a night.
I see.
Come to think of it, I'm invited to a dance workshop on that day.
A workshop?
Yeah.
It's kind of like a camp-in with the dance company I always go to.
Instructors come, we take lessons and choreograph.
I see…
If you weren't gonna be around, I should've gone.
Is it too late to go now?
Yeah, I think it's past the deadline.
Man, I'll have to stay home again.
I'll try to come home as soon as possible.
Really?
Really.
I don't really like those kinds of group activities.
You feel so soft and nice.
There!
Oh, no.
I'm sorry, Hasumi-san.
Okay, okay!
You're not going to play?
Umm… it hurts when I get sunburnt.
Then, I'll take a rest too.
No, it's okay. You don't have to worry about me.
Please have fun with everyone.
Then, later.
There's no way I can say, "Actually, I've never played tennis before."
I would never lose in aikidou.
Wow! It feels like we're underwater, doesn't it?
Yes.
Hasumi-san, I heard that there are seals over there. Let's go see them!
Oh, wait…
Chief didn't come after all.
He's too stubborn.
Never mind about that. Ishida-kun, do you know how to understand women through a barbeque?
No, what't that?
In this world, humans can be separated into a few categories.
The first is…
"Eaters"
"Cookers"
"Those that never cook but get to be served".
I see!
Usually, men can't really tell the difference between
the "Cookers" and "those that never cook but get to be served".
They're happy just by being served,
so they don't try to delve into the deeper psychology of things.
On top of that, those who are served and don't cook have a lot of time on their hands.
So they can engage in fun conversations and raise the spirit of a place.
I see…
That's where the snare is.
Man, I still have so much to learn!
Well, personally I like the Cookers.
It's true that her movements seem very feminine and family-oriented.
Yeah…
But you know what? The most hardworking person is over there.
The dullest type of people, the "Cutters".
Wow, she's cutting. Iwaya-san's cutting a lot.
The way she cuts is pretty impressive.
Yeah, well… I can assure you that she's great at cooking, too.
Man… I envy you, Hasumi-san!
She really is something. I have so much respect for Iwaya-san.
But that kind of perfect people who can do everything
kind of tire you out when you're together, don't they?
It's like you can't relax…
She does have a point.
When she gets her work done so well, it becomes hard to warm up to her.
That's true.
She doesn't even let you help her.
It's fine. I can get more done when I'm doing it by myself anyway.
You know… my skin is so sensitive that
I can't do any kind of washing unless I have special gloves on.
Oh, really? That must be a pain.
I think it's starting to get itchy again…
I may have some kind of ointment back at the lodge.
No, I'm fine. Don't worry about it at all.
Why is he so nice to her?
Hasumi-san, I barbequed this meat for you! Please have some.
Hey, hey! Give me some, too.
There are a lot more over there.
Oh, I know! Let's all take a picture! Shall we? A picture!
Oh, Hasumi-san… move over here.
I want to be next to him, too!
Iwaya-san! Why don't you join us in the picture?
Huh? Oh, I'm sorry. I don't really like pictures very much.
Oh, all right.
Then everyone, come in. Here…
Over here! Hurry, hurry!
Everyone pose! Uriyama-san, please raise your head!
This is why I didn't want to come… on such a stupid vacation.
Excuse me, this dog brought a letter to an employee in our department.
Oh, where is Iwaya-san today?
She's on the employee vacation.
Oh, really?
Emily, here, here… welcome back.
When they're around, it's loud and obnoxious, but once they're gone, it gets lonely.
Well, why don't you stay and have some tea?
Thank you very much.
Hasumi-san, here you go.
Oh, thank you.
How about you, Iwaya-san? A drink?
Thanks.
Oh…
A cup?
Is Momo staying home today?
Huh? Oh, yes.
My Carlos, too. But cats can stand one night alone, won't dogs get lonely?
That's true.
But your younger brother can take care of it, can't he?
What? A younger brother? Iwaya-san has a younger brother?
Mine is fine. It's fine.
That's so true. Pets actually aren't as lonely as we think they may be.
Oh, really?
Yeah, totally.
Like the last time she disappeared… when she came back, her fur looked oddly nice.
I guess they have their own little world.
She probably has a boyfriend. Even though her master doesn't have one.
You piss me off, Ishidacchi!
I wonder how Momo's doing…
Man, I have to stay home again.
Hasumi-san, I think I'm feeling a little tipsy.
I wonder why I'm in this place.
Miss, if you are leaving, would you like me to call a taxi for you?
Oh, that's okay. I can get one myself.
Hey, wait!
Damn…
30 more minutes…
Maybe I should just take the bus.
Hello, Sumire-chan?
Hello? Hello~?
Momo?
Huh? Is something wrong, Sumire-chan?
It can't be…
Hey~
Hello? Can you hear me?
Can you hear me, Sumire-chan? Hello?
You're kidding me! Sumire-chan?
Momo!
Ouch! That hurts!
Sumire-chan, you smell like sake!
Why are you here, you little rascal?!
Why are you here?
That's what I'd like to ask you!
I'm here for that thing… the dance workshop I told you about.
My friend submitted an application for me and they called me.
We're having it at the hall over there.
You're kidding me, it's so close!
Oh, yeah. I remember you said yours was in Hakone, too.
What are you doing here like this?
The icebreaker was kind of boring, so I stepped out for a while.
Were you trying to go home?
Not really…
Well, yeah.
Then I'll go home, too.
What are you talking about? You've got to participate in the workshop, so you should stay.
No, it doesn't matter. I was able to get some tips this afternoon already.
It's not okay! Don't worry about me.
Here.
Sumire-chan, you only have to say the words "Let's go home".
Because you're my master.
Let's go home…
shall we?
Wait just a minute. I'll go grab my stuff right away.
That surprised me.
Hasumi-senpai!
I finally found you, Iwaya.
You suddenly disappeared. Did something happen?
I decided to sober myself up with a walk.
With your baggage?
Huh?
Oh, this… it has material for my work and some valuables.
So I was afraid to leave them behind.
Oh, okay.
I was worried that you might be angry at me for something.
What?
You seemed to be avoiding me during dinner, too.
You're imagining things…
Of course I'm angry…
I'm furious about the whole thing with Fukushima-san.
But…
It's really nothing.
I was just a little tired, that's all.
Really?
Yes!
Everyone wanted to go for karaoke, so they went out to town.
I see.
What do you want to do? Shall we go on a date with just the two of us?
Oh… but…
There they are!
That's where the two of you have been!
Gosh, everyone's been looking for you!
Let's go, Hasumi-san!
I thought you'd left already, Iwaya-san.
Wait for me!
Iwaya, let's go.
Yes!
Where did you go?
For a walk.
Carrying your luggage?
Yeah.
It's almost time for the free lessons. Aren't you coming?
I have a rash, so just tell them I'm asleep.
Are you avoiding me?
No, not at all.
How are things with you? And Junpei…
I…
Maybe I'll skip lessons, too.
I can't even go home now.
I wonder how Momo's doing.
Umm…
It seems I've had too much to drink, so I'll be going back to my room now.
Excuse me.
I guess there won't be anyone around at this hour.
Wow.
First off, I have to apologize.
Mo—
Gosh…
You're practicing after all.
You're actually pretty serious.
You're too nosy.
I couldn't sleep, so I thought moving around would help.
You know… I like it when you look troubled like that.
Because you always act so happy-go-lucky and it pisses me off.
What's that supposed to mean?
Even though you're actually very lonely inside.
You're the one who pisses me off.
What?
Just…
Just now, I thought I saw a woman outside the window.
A woman?
Oh… come to think of it, the hall owner's daughter committed suicide a long time ago.
Stop it! Don't tell scary stories like that at night.
Then why don't you go to sleep? You have to wake up early tomorrow anyway.
After hearing a story like that, I can't go to sleep.
I had nothing to worry about.
It seems like he's having fun.
Even cats have a different home that the owner doesn't know about.
And Momo's a human after all.
Oh, a chick!
Hey, sweetheart, where are you from?
A pet having a woman?!
Huh?
It's 10000 years too early for that brat!
Sorry!
He doesn't even have money and has asthma. He can't even do anything on his own…!
Pets actually aren't as lonely as we think they may be.
I guess they have their own little world.
Iwaya, are you okay?
Oh, Senpai.
I was worried, so I came after you. But I lost sight of you.
I'm sorry for making you worry.
No. I have to apologize for bringing you on a trip you didn't want to be on.
That's not true…
But it makes me feel bad when your expression is like that.
Oh, no… I'm really fine.
Senpai?
I wonder how I can make you feel more at ease…
Can you tell me?
Hey, Takeshi…
Sorry.
Hey! Wait a second, Takeshi.
Stop running away all the time!
Sorry, Junpei.
But, deep down…
deep down I like Takeshi after all.
I like him so much I can't forget about him.
I don't care anymore.
Wait…
Senpai, are you drunk?
I'm not drunk.
We can't do this in a place like this…
Then, can I stay over at your house when we get back tomorrow?
Oh… but if it's too sudden, my pet…
Pets aren't allowed in your apartment, right?
If you're so nice to your pet,
I may just get jealous of it.
Stop…
No!
I'm sorry, but I just can't… in a place like this.
I'm sorry.
You're right, not in a place like this.
I guess I am a little drunk.
Then I'll go buy some tea or something.
Don't worry about it.
No, it's fine. It's just right here and I'm pretty thirsty too.
Active, aren't we?
You too.
What are you going to do tomorrow?
What?
If Hasumi-kun's coming over, I can go somewhere else.
Why? Were you listening?
It's fine, I'll just turn him down.
Don't worry about it, I'll just disappear for a few days.
What are you talking about? You don't have anywhere to go.
Of course I do.
It's no problem at all.
And I have some money.
Besides, I have these looks. So I'm sure there are a lot of people who'll be willing to feed me.
Even if I don't have you to look after me, I won't die or anything.
Is that so?
Then you don't have to come back for a while.
Don't come home!
Okay, I won't.
You can make out without worries… not in a place like that.
It's probably a good idea to get sex out of the way as soon as possible.
What do you mean by that?
Then…
Goodbye.
Never come back, you stupid pet!
Stupid…
Why?
Why did it turn out like this?
We've never gotten into a fight before.
You only have to say the words "Let's go home".
Let's go home…
shall we?
If we had gone home then…
Momo, you can't eat that until after dinner!
Right about now, as usual, we'd be…
That hurt, damn it…
Why?
Oh, I'm so sleepy.
It's pretty hard to come back to work straight after a zengen.
That's why I told you it wasn't worth going.
If it was only our department, we could have just gone over the weekend.
You're kidding me, Ishidacchi! You have to go for an interview now?
You still smell like sake. Chew some gum.
Hey, Uriyama! Uriyama, wake up!
Even if I don't have you to look after me, I won't die or anything.
Don't come home!
Okay, I won't.
I'm sure he's back home by now.
Actually, I'm sorry…
Today I don't feel so well.
I see… all right then.
Rest well with Momo-chan.
Yes.
Maybe…
What he just said was ironic.
Whatever it may be, there was no way such an odd lifestyle could continue like that.
But now…
On a day like this, when my head hurts…
I have to spend it with Momo.
[sign]No pets allowed
Hello, Iwaya-san.
Were you on vacation?
Why?
Why aren't pets allowed?
Oh… Well, that's just a rule.
Shouldn't it be okay
if it doesn't cause anyone any trouble?
Why is it wrong?
Well, it's just…
Are you all right? You look a little sick.
You don't have to say anything!
It's fine. If it's just fish or birds, it's fine.
However, other animals, such as dogs and cats,
will damage the facilities on the premises.
And they'll bark and bite!
Bite?
Yes!
I understand. Thank you for your hard work.
Oh, Iwaya-san! I knew it! You have a pet, don't you?!
Yes, one human being.
What?
Maybe she got pregnant…
Oh, I guess he's just not home yet.
[sign]Momo
LOVE
Why?
He really…
He really won't come home…