What?
I came to pick you up, since it's 10 o'clock.
Oops... I totally forgot...
Umm...
Wait a minute, all right? I'll contact you later.
My name is Momo.
I've been cared for at this place since April, as a pet.
Or should I say, I was cared for...
Good morning, Yuri-chan!
What are you doing here?
To tell the truth, actually...
Oh, long time no see. Good morning.
Excuse me.
I'll see you off. You're coming back during the weekend, right?
That's right.
See you later, Ran. Be good.
Be good.
Goodbye, honey.
I should be going now.
Goodbye.
So, what happened?
What kind of a final night did you spend together?
You can forget the little details,
I just want to know the end result.
Hey...
As for the end result...
I ended up telling him.
Huh? What?
I told him, "Don't go."
Don't go.
Don't leave me behind.
This is bad, Momo-kun.
What I'm getting at is...
I ended up doing it.
When I woke up, Momo was lying naked next to me.
And...
I ran away by myself.
You are my pet
10. Journey from paradise
I had planned on seeing him off with a smile.
I thought I'd have to say goodbye with a smile.
But it just rolled out of my mouth, "Don't go."
But when she told me not to go with tears in her eyes,
I couldn't think of anything anymore.
He suddenly seemed so precious.
And then the brakes just wouldn't work, and...
I just let everything happen naturally.
Meaning... things just happened, one after another, in the heat of things...
The heat of things?
Yes, I think it was just the heat and mood of things.
Because it was the last night, I think both our emotions were kind of high.
I think that's why things happened the way they did.
And, why are you here right now?
But when I woke up, she wasn't there anymore.
Isn't that harsh? No letter, no breakfast, no nothing!
Don't keep asking for breakfast even until the last minute.
But you see...
She's the one who told me not to go, yet she's the one who left.
It's total abandonment. She didn't even bring her phone.
Even though it's already time for me to leave.
Because I didn't know what kind of a face I should greet him with in the morning.
My dignity as a pet owner is tattered.
Why are you talking about dignity now? That's not the issue.
But...
You go home right now, and tell him...
"Are you going to pick Germany or me?! Of course me, right?!", and stop him.
I can't say such an unreasonable thing.
You did that last night because you still felt an attachment, didn't you?
Plus, it's not right to crush a young man's illustrious future with my own selfish demands.
He's eight years younger than me!
That's not what you were thinking when you told him not to go.
But, maybe...
I might just have been used to fill Hasumi-kun's void.
Momo might have thought to do it just for the sake of a memory.
She might have just been playing me at the last moment.
He could be home by now, feeling refreshed.
How do you get such a tragic outlook on things?
But...
It still made me happy.
We shouldn't have done it.
You are no longer able to believe in your partner.
You've lost confidence in your own attractiveness.
Even relationships that have been going well can turn sour after reaching a sexual encounter.
It happens often. I told you to keep him off the set! Forget it...
The reason for this is that...
Love is an uncertain thing.
Because people are afraid of losing it,
they become cowardly and servile.
In other words...
once you eat the apple,
you cannot return to paradise.
Welcome back.
I'm home.
Sorry I left without saying anything.
You were leaving... right?
Yeah... Well...
I wanted to say goodbye to you,
but you weren't there.
I see.
Thanks for everything up until now.
It was really fun, these past two and a half months.
Yeah, me too.
It was really fun. I'm glad I was found by such a good person.
Right around here. That's where the box was.
Oh, really?
It was so heavy! I pulled it with all my strength.
I can only remember it like I remember a dream.
Oh, but the soft rice was striking. It was delicious!
Be careful with your asthma.
And your injury, you always push yourself too much.
You shouldn't push yourself too much either, Sumire-chan.
Who, me?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Don't try too hard with everything.
You act too tough as well.
When you want to cry, it's okay to cry with someone around.
I'm not so weak as to cry in front of people.
But, if you can, stay the way you are...
Don't change too much.
What do you mean by that?
Make sure things go well with Hasumi-kun.
It's not too late.
I wonder about that.
I'll try talking to him about it again.
I'm glad I was your pet.
Me too. I'm glad I got to live with you.
See you again someday.
See you someday.
Then...
Bye-bye.
Okay! I'll be your pet.
So, I'm Momo.
I was very happy with my reward.
It's good. It's really delicious!
I really like having you shampoo my hair.
Welcome home!
I said it.
I said goodbye properly. Didn't I, Momo?
With a smile...
Hello.
Are you going somewhere?
If you're looking for Sumire-chan, she's at home.
I actually wanted to talk to you.
Thanks.
It's fine, I'll answer anything.
Go ahead.
There are so many things,
I don't know where to start.
From the point that a human becomes a pet, it's beyond my understanding.
I'll say this in defense of my master...
Your master?
I think a pet is different from a bum who just lives off someone's money.
How are they different?
You were being cared for, right?
Yeah, but rather than a bum...
I think I was more like a blanket.
A blanket?
Yeah, like Linus' baby blanket.
Something that's always close by, you can pull it when you want, and wipe your tears and stuff.
I think a pet is like an evolved form of the healing comfort which blankets exude.
It's alive, and has some feelings too.
I don't quite understand, but you're neither a blanket nor an animal, right?
That's why I'm leaving.
At one point, I wished I could just be a blanket.
Then I wouldn't be afraid of jealousy or loneliness.
But at the same time, I wouldn't be able to feel happiness, fun, nor moved.
So that's why I thought I'd go back to being human.
Well, that's basically it.
Actually, I also...
once thought I'd like to become a rock that lies at the bottom of the river.
It seems so cool. And on rainy days, it will roll a little.
And it can be a place where little fish stop to rest.
I thought that would be a much more free and meaningful existence than myself at the time.
I think it was the day before I found out I got into Tokyo University.
That's kind of an unpleasant memory.
Oh... it's become such a somber topic, huh?
It may be rude of me,
but I'm not going to apologise.
That I lied. I don't feel like I've wronged you, Hasumi-kun.
But I do feel sorry about the fact that I caused her to end up lying.
Well... it's over, anyhow...
Now she can become happy in a normal way.
Although I'm sure it was going well enough until now.
So..
I don't plan on breaking up with Iwaya.
I'm actually sort of glad that she told me honestly.
Because she's bad at lying.
All this time, I kind of sensed that something was amiss.
Although I never would have guessed that the pet was a human.
It was a shock to find out that she was living with a young man.
But I know that she's not so smooth as to be able to double deal and cheat.
As I've been watching her since she entered the business.
I see...
I believe in her.
And I will gradually break down the wall with time.
Eventually, I hope that we can arrive at a relationship where we can truly trust each other.
So it was nothing...
You're so young, but you look as if you're tired of living life.
Yeah, I guess I don't even have the time to be tired.
How about what you said to me when you told me you liked her?
Was that also a lie?
Yeah, it was a lie.
You're young after all.
Well, don't worry, and just go do your best in Germany.
Like I need you to tell me that.
All right, take care.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Then, next we can take it into the courtyard.
Oh, that would be nice. Then we can include Yoshie.
Let's go, Yoshie.
Hey, kitty, aren't you glad we found a good daddy for you?
Senpai!
It'll get lonely around here, Takeshi.
What happened to that lady?
Oh, I said a proper goodbye to her a little while ago.
I think she'll be able to wait if it's just three years.
Nah, I couldn't help but eat the apple.
An apple from paradise which I wasn't supposed to eat.
Why, Takeshi, don't you know?
The story of mankind began from the moment they left paradise.
Please sit down.
Umm... would you like to have some coffee? You have night duty after this.
No, I think I'll have some beer.
I'm kidding.
I just thought that we may not be able to be honest with one another if we don't drink.
I'm truly sorry.
For lying to you like that.
No, more than the lie...
At that time, you remember how you said you had a good relationship with him?
Those words kind of bothered me.
Exactly what kind of a relationship do you mean by a good relationship?
I think, at the beginning, I just felt like a volunteer.
But maybe he felt that way, too.
I really liked him...
I'm so sad.
It's just that two people are better than one.
And eventually, he became an indispensable existence.
And those were not feelings of love?
No, because he was a pet.
I realised the other day, while I was looking in the mirror...
when I'm with Junpei, I'm kind of cute.
What are you talking about?
I look happy, unlike when I was with you.
Was I that much of a bad guy?
Yeah, totally.
Well, I wasn't so nice either.
I really liked you, Rumi.
What do you mean? That's why you're still a child.
After three years, I'm going to be a much better woman, and I'm going to be the one who'll reject you.
After three years...
Sorry to keep you waiting!
You're late, Junpei!
What were you guys talking about?
About how I can't see myself three years from now.
You're going to be a world famous professional dancer, right?
Well, you'll never know what could happen in the span of three years.
You think so?
Something else might come your way.
The world may come to an end by that time.
He's been pretty pessimistic like this since this morning.
Sorry, Junpei, but even if the world comes to an end,
I'd like to believe that friendship will never die.
Me too.
Then me too.
I guess I'm childish after all.
Right now, I just got this pang of sadness.
I'm kidding, I'll beat you one of these days.
Hey, wait, Junpei!
Good luck with everything.
Later.
Bye-bye.
I don't expect you to forgive me just by my apology.
But my feelings for you aren't a lie.
I've liked you since Kofu...
I believe you.
I hope...
Little by little...
I can come to show you my true self.
So even if distance sets us apart...
is it all right if I still like you?
I guess I can't forgive you after all.
I seriously liked you, and I believed in you. That's why I can't forgive you.
Maybe I'm not mature enough to get rid of all my doubts.
Is that so...
Of course... I deserve it, since I did such a selfish thing...
Besides...
Even if I felt like I wanted to protect you,
I don't think I want to become a blanket.
Oh, umm... but I did notice that.
Oh, I'm sorry.
See, you apologised again. You really don't grow up, do you?
I'm sorry.
Get a hold of yourself.
The next time we meet, we can just be good colleagues.
Goodbye.
Senpai...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry...
It may be rude of me, but I'm not going to apologise.
I don't plan on breaking up with Iwaya.
I won't apologise for lying either.
At any time,
the world is still revolving.
However much I distress,
I must move forward once again.
Good morning.
Wow, so much work...
Oh, Iwaya. The cover story for next week needs to be redone.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Shoot, I better submit it soon.
They won't look over it until the evening paper is done.
Iwaya-san,
it was decided for today.
We're all going out for a drink tonight.
What?
Oh, I'm not sure if I can go.
What?! Hey, don't say such a thing!
That's right, it's also a farewell party for Fukushima-san.
Farewell party?
Yes. Please come, Iwaya-san.
Well, everyone! Today's meeting place is written here!
To those who wish to seek counselling in the Counselling Room on the 14th floor:
6/14 (Sat) – 6/18 (Wed)
I will be out on an Employee Training Workshop
Out?
Does he have employees?
Now that everyone is here, please raise your glass in one hand. And... TOAST!
Thank you for all your hard work!
Thank you!
Do you remember that journalist from Maiasa Newspaper, Ikeuchi Noriko?
Oh, yeah, she returned to the company around the same time I did.
Yeah, she's my age, and I heard she got divorced last year.
And I heard she's now living with a young man.
People around her say that she owns a pet.
She takes care of everything, including food fees.
I understand that she has expensive tastes, but that's a little absurd.
That's the worst. That journalist is bad, but so is that boy.
What kind of poor judgement does he have to be fed and supported by a woman? How pitiful.
I don't like it either. It mars the dignity of men.
Is that really so? I think the whole idea of
"because he's a man, because she's a woman" is old-fashioned in the first place.
As long as they're supporting each other well, it shouldn't matter who's the one paying the living fees.
Oh... apologies.
Yeah, that's true. I think it's totally okay to have a woman treat me.
No way, I'd rather have a man treat me.
As usual, this woman ruins the spirit of the gathering.
Although you say that, you're going to go with him, aren't you?
No, that has already ended.
What?
You're kidding me? Already ended... do you mean you broke up with Hasumi-san?
I'm going to go back to the office. I still have work left to do.
See, you made her go like that.
But after I told them, I feel like something's been lifted off my chest.
You didn't tell Hasumi-san about your pet, did you?
Even though I intentionally didn't say anything...
I couldn't hide it from him.
Hasumi-senpai and Momo, they both mean a lot to me.
There was no way I could choose between the two.
You should have just deceived them somehow, and worked it to your advantage.
Maybe you're best off alone.
Perhaps you're right.
But I'll thank you anyway. Thanks for not saying anything.
It's no big deal. I just didn't want to hurt him.
What?
You can laugh if you want.
But before I knew it, I really fell for him.
I had the chance to say it so many times.
But...
I've decided now.
I'll go to Rio de Janeiro.
What?
Don't you understand?
He's going to be feeling the hurt of a broken relationship in the lonely city of a foreign country.
This is the biggest chance I'll ever get.
I think the unconditional feelings that I have for him now will win his heart.
I will become happy.
I see.
What? You're going back?
Because I can't become free like you,
so I think I'll have to be in the company of those members a little while longer.
I'll try harder, so it'll become a more comfortable place for me.
Although everything has disappeared,
I am still not alone.
I continue living, being supported by... and at the same time, supporting people.
I'm so excited about Hawaii.
Do you feel restless without your Chihuahua?
No, not at all.
Are you sure you can really be happy with me?
Yes, I found my new job already, too.
Hey, over there, are the sausages all frankfurts?
No, because it's the real thing. I think
you will be able to enjoy quite a variety of sausages.
Wow, I'm lucky! I wonder if they have curry there, too?
I haven't researched that yet.
Why haven't you researched it?
I feel something.
What?
I went over, and saw him feigning sleep with his Noh mask on.
I'm helpless without Momo.
The pet got sick of me and left. That is all.
It seems he's going to Frankfurt.
Momo!
Momo-chan?
Huh?
I knew it!
Umm... who...
Well... you know...
That's a wonderful outfit.
Thanks.
Oh, a gentle smile.
What?
Umm... exactly who are you?
The path you are about to follow is probably the right path.
So you should be able to go forward without doubts.
Yes.
Takeshi-san, we don't have much time.
But if there is even the slightest possibility of regret, it is not altogether a waste to doubt.
People are born as small individuals,
and they continually wish to grow bigger.
They have been living their lives wishing to grow bigger and bigger.
But is that truly something we need?
What are you anyway? Part of some cult?
But what does that matter?
As long as we have a free heart,
we shouldn't have to fear whether we can grow bigger or not.
You can spoil yourself, you can be weak.
Because fundamentally, humans are weak.
Although we may be weak... without stretching ourselves...
As long as we look around us... the place that is always close to us, is actually the most precious.
I hope that you too can find your one and only place in life.
I wonder who that was.
Takeshi-san?
Oh, wha— Takeshi-san?
I know that person.
If I'm correct, he's a famous dancer.
Oh, is that so?
Yes.
Maybe I have done something horrible for Japan's, I mean, the world's artistic culture.
I think it's okay to choose that one love rather than the world's culture.
Because it's very difficult to find your place in life.
I don't have money, so here is fine.
Thank you very much.
Where is the train station?
Oh, over there.
Takeshi-san!
Soon...
Soon I'll see her again.
Takeshi-san!
Something about staying home is painful.
I hate to admit it, but the kitchen, bathtub, toilet... Everywhere carries memories of Momo.
He may be feeling just as lonely.
I don't know about that.
He may be perfectly fine, and could be some German woman's pet by now.
They seem to have nice bodies over there anyway.
I think he's doing his dance lessons like he's supposed to.
I don't like Germany. They have beer, Beethoven, Oliver Kahn...
And I was just thinking how I would like to go to the hot springs for a night.
Hot springs? Sounds nice.
Isn't it?
I reserved a pretty nice lodge.
You should come along next time if you want.
Sure, I'll go.
What an eventful three months it's been...
You know, Ran grew 3 cm in three months!
One season passed, hasn't it?
Yes, and another season is just beginning.
You were just having a slightly longer dream.
Yeah.
All right, later.
It's not a dream at all...
because I can vividly remember Momo's kiss.
This is bad, I better go.
Hello?
I know this is rather sudden, but your pet got into an accident.
Pet?
Fortunately, it wasn't so serious as to take his life. However...
Hello? Hello?
Momo.
I hurt my arm.
So...
will you give me a bath again?
Really...
Then first off, I need to cancel my reservation at the hot springs.
Welcome home.
I'm home, Sumire-chan.
Welcome back, Momo.
I have someone whom I can show my weaknesses, and even my most embarrassing side.
Because that is like a miracle, I will never let go of this hand again.
Well, it's been a while since then,
but every day has been passing by as if it were meant to be like this.
I look after his needs, while he sleeps and dances.
We haven't done anything sexual since then.
Apparently, our relationship is a little different from lovers,
but I think it may not be that of a pet and owner anymore either...
I see.
But perhaps, as we spend more time together,
things may change gradually.
That's why it's all right. For example,
she'll call me "Takeshi", maybe 1 out of 10 times, when she calls my name.
In that way, I think it'll change gradually.
Do you think you two will eventually become lovers?
I don't know.
It may become a totally new kind of relationship.
Well, it doesn't really matter what she calls me.
As long as we're always together and it's comfortable, that's enough.
I'll take this for you.
May I sit next to you?
Sure.
Fukushima-san?!
What, Hasumi-san?!
Wow, you surprised me.
You know, I decided to learn samba dancing in Rio de Janeiro.
Oh, is that so?
Doesn't that guy look familiar?
Really? He's in the beginner class, isn't he?
Wow, your lines look good. And your joints are properly separated.
Yes, I used to do classic dance.
I got a lot together. It's hot.
Oh, Iwaya-san. Welcome back.
Hello. Thank you for your hard work.
Takeshi has come home already.
Thank you.
I'm home.
Welcome back!
Momo, don't jump on me like that. The flan will break.
Oh! Flan?! Can I open it?
No, it's for after dinner.
Why? Can't I open it a little now?
Wow, it looks good!
What else?
Umm... can you get me the eggs?
All right, how many?
Two.
Hey, can I break this one?
Are you sure you can do it?
Sure thing, let me do it.
Oh, man. The shell fell in!
Are you serious?! Ow! I cut myself!
Are you okay? Let me see it.
That hurts!
Wait, don't move!
Stop it!
You have to get it out.
I said, stop it!
You have to get it out, or else it won't stop.
Wait... Ouch! That hurts, Momo!