Hasumi-senpa—
Mo—
This may not be the right time to say it, but my name is Momo.
If I were to explain this situation simply, it would be like this:
One month ago, I was found unconscious by Sumire-chan,
and since then, I've been staying here as her pet.
Bath time and meals are the best!
But sex is forbidden.
But recently, an old flame of my master's reappeared.
That's how it is, so back to the show.
Momo, be quiet!
That was…?
Huh?
I'm sorry, my dog got excited.
A dog? Oh yeah, you mentioned you had a pet.
Yes, and that pet is such a pet…
Even at night, it's so noisy. And on top of that, vicious.
Really… and it's very unfriendly to strangers.
I see.
So, I'm sorry. Maybe you should…
Oh, all right…
But I want you to go out with me.
What?
Back then, I didn't want to say anything and leave you hanging because I was going overseas,
but now I can say it.
I want to…
Yes?
Yes, it is I who should say so…
Oh, I mean…
me too.
That's great.
Well, I don't want your dog to get jealous of me anymore, so…
Yes, I'm sorry.
Good night.
This warm feeling is so nostalgic.
Gosh, Momo! Why were you spying?!
It's not like I wanted to spy on you guys.
I was just staying at home, obediently waiting for your return.
When I heard your footsteps,
I rushed towards the front door to greet you, and I saw that…
that unsightly kiss…
He was even using his tongue! I didn't want to see that!
No, really… even I was surprised.
That senpai would suddenly do such a thing…
Really? You looked like you were pretty comfortable.
I have 20/20 vision in each eye. Isn't that impressive?
And I can even see your true feelings right now.
What?
Right now, you're thinking,
"Now my mind is too preoccupied with my senpai.
I don't really have time to be chatting with Momo."
That's what you're thinking, right?
Huh?
Wha— What?
What are you talking about? There's no way…
I was so worried about your injury…
How did he figure that out?
It's true. I mean, the unrequited love
of 4 years ago has finally come true!
So I don't really have the right
state of mind to be thinking about other things.
See? So I'll give you a bath. We have to wash your hair.
I guess I can cover it up by giving him a bath.
I'll have to keep him in a good mood.
It's all right.
Wait… Momo, your bath!
It's fine, I can do it alone.
What was that? He was the one who dropped my futons.
Hello…?
Hello, Yuri-chan. Is this a good time?
No, it's not. Make it short.
Understood.
Today, at approximately 11 pm,
Hasumi-senpai saw me home after our first date, and he asked me out.
Umm, can't I listen to this tomorrow?
No, but Momo saw me!
And he's kind of pouting now.
Throw him away. You have a boyfriend now.
What?
But boyfriends and pets are different.
But your pet is of the human species, and a male too!
Thank you for the prompt answer.
Well, I knew all along…
that Sumire-chan only regarded me as her old dog, Momo.
What is it with Momo?
What is this?!
All the cigarettes I bought are gone…
Why is this here?
What is this…?
Sumire-chan is STUPID!!
Momo!
Momo, come down! Momo!
You are my pet
3. Boyfriend vs. (male) pet
Something's wrong.
This morning I made him curry, but he wouldn't wake up.
I went over and saw him feigning sleep, with his Noh-mask on.
Plus, there were mini tomatoes placed in each of my commuting shoes.
And I accidentally crushed them…
I see.
What could be wrong?
Yes?
I'm sorry to interrupt your counseling session.
That's all right, she is not a patient.
There's a telephone call from the professor.
Oh, please tell him that I will call him back as soon as possible.
I understand.
Isn't that the girl working at the coffeehouse on the first floor?
I scouted her because I needed an assistant.
Oh, okay.
And, about your problem,
it doesn't need counseling. You need a pet advisor.
True, I told you to come to the 14th floor,
but I don't have time for this.
Today's schedule is full of appointments.
So it seems.
Yes.
But you seem very close with her.
Oh, with her…
it's just a business-like relationship.
No, with her.
I felt like I was beginning to understand your feelings
about bringing a pet along to No Man's Island.
Because…
my dog was also there for me
when I was going through difficult or depressing times.
I see.
So, as I thought, I don't want to let it go.
There's this train of thought:
what modern women need is not a lifelong spouse, but a lifelong friendship with a pet.
Think about it this way.
Everyday, there are various things that frustrate you, giving you stress.
Society, your job, your superior, your subordinates,
allergies, the phone that doesn't ring, your happy-looking girl friends, everything.
Not everything in this world is on your side.
Yes, not even the one you love.
When you think that the person you love is healing your heart,
it's just a happy misjudgement.
Long ago, women would work hard for men, for their families.
There was a time when that was considered to be good fortune.
But that time has come to an end.
You don't want to feel stress from other people when you go home.
But being alone is lonely. For that, they are there.
Am I wrong?
I think I understand that point of view.
My pet always accepts me unconditionally.
Right? You will probably be single for the rest of your life.
What?
You've become addicted to your pet.
A very convenient roommate.
Convenient?
Yes, convenient.
When we men hear that a single working woman has a pet,
this is what we think:
"Oh, it's over for that woman."
They're going to be single for the rest of their lives,
and they're trying to use a pet to fill the place of a man.
I mean that's a lifestyle, too…
What am I saying? That is also…
That'll be enough, thank you.
I have more to say…
I will never come to the 14th floor again.
Your pet is a male, isn't it?
It's dangerous to love your pet too much.
He is, after all, only a pet.
He may serve as family, but he's not human.
Please do not forget that.
My pet is a human!
That is something I can't say.
Umm, I couldn't help but overhear…
Something similar happened with my dog, Goma-chan.
He did various mischievous things.
Really?
Yes.
He would purposely poop on my clothes,
and gnaw on my favorite furniture.
I heard that when their master's attention shifts elsewhere, they'll feel very uneasy.
So at times like that, it's better to treat them gently rather than scold them.
Gently…
He's really cute. Please take a look.
Its eyes are like mine and its ears are also very big.
You're the one who's cute.
Hey, you really haven't gotten laid? With your master?
That again? It's getting annoying.
But she's an incredible woman.
Really? She's expressionless, and don't you think she's too big?
Hey, but don't you feel like you want to? Living together and all that.
Well, if you're asking whether I want to or not, it would be a lie to say I didn't want to.
But if you're asking, wouldn't you have to in order for the relationship to begin, that's not how it is either.
I see.
But that kissy bastard!
Well, I don't want your dog to get jealous of me anymore, so…
Why would I be jealous, stupid?!
Sumire-chan bathes me!
I get to zip up the back of her dress, and even get to see her bra!
I even get to see her in pajamas!
Everyone's watching! Calm down, Takeshi-kun!
I am calm…
I'm naturally a cool guy.
But in any case, it's only two more months, right?
Huh?
You said you were going to try out for the upcoming performance.
Oh…!
Geez, where did your cool go?
So deep down you're jealous, aren't you?
Maybe I am…
… as a dog.
You!
Oh, Takeshi-san.
I see you've found me out.
What do you mean, "I see you've found me out"?
Why are you holding that trash bag?
Don't tell me…
As you can see, I live here. At Sensei's request.
What the…
I told you guys to leave me alone.
Are you living with that woman?
What are you talking about?
I don't know what you're trying to do, but if you try to mess up my life now…
I'll kill you.
Better to be gentle than to scold them…
I'm home!
Masa Saito's final battle got taped over!
Momo, I know you're there!
I won't get mad, so please come down.
Hey, Momo! I'll give you a bath, so come here.
I'll give you treatment and a scalp massage.
After that, I'll clean out your ears.
Please, Momo, stop being mad at me. You're a good boy.
Sumire-chan's a liar.
What?
You said you wouldn't go out with anyone for a while.
I thought so too, really.
That as long as I had my job and a pet, it would be enough.
It's true!
So just because I have a boyfriend doesn't mean I'm going to kick you out all of a sudden.
You can stay—
If you really want to…
I'll let you wash my hair.
Gosh, you silly boy! Don't make me worry like that!
That hurts, Sumire-chan.
That hurts…
Mmm… it feels good.
Today, I was given a new special article project to work on.
It's kind of like a big job. Seems like the animal costume article was a big success.
Wow, that's good. That's really great.
Momo, where were you before you came here?
I didn't tell you?
I got into a fight with my parents and left home.
Oh, is that so?
Actually, I've been learning classical ballet since I was two years old.
I've even been trained overseas.
I never grew any taller and was never able to get the role of a prince.
In modern dance, there are all sorts of dance moves and it doesn't matter if I'm short.
There's a lot of variety, so it's interesting too. But my parents were against it, so I left home.
I see.
It feels so good!
The moment you stand on the stage, the atmosphere and the feeling you get;
no matter how many times I do it, I still get goose bumps from the joy I feel.
But this is nice too.
I love getting shampoos from Sumire-chan!
Oh, really?
Oh, sorry. Just wait a second, stay where you are.
I'm sorry for calling this late.
The Brazilian president suddenly decided to come to Japan and I've been running around with the other reporters.
I see…
You seem pretty busy tonight.
And I was wondering…
Will I be able to see you the day after tomorrow, before my night duty?
The day after tomorrow?
Yes, it's all right. I have that day off.
That's good.
Actually, I bought something for you.
It's the Dog Language Interpreting Device that was so popular last year.
Dog language?
Yup! Actually, I like dogs a lot.
Back in my hometown, I have two at my house.
Right now, I live in an apartment where pets aren't allowed.
I see…
my appartment doesn't allow it either.
So, can I come visit it, your pet?
My brother's pet, Mirumiru-chan.
Mirumiru-chan's getting so excited!
This is the towel he always uses.
Apparently, if you lay him here, he'll calm down.
Thanks. I'm sorry I asked for such a favor.
Really! I don't know why I have to help you protect your pet.
Really! I don't want to be protected by this old lady either.
What?
That's why I told you to throw away this pet!
Don't fight, you two.
But Sumire-chan, you're the weird one.
Bringing a dog in to replace me, and trying to cover things up.
So true.
You're a Tokyo University graduate, yet you could only come up with such childish tricks.
I can't help it. I couldn't think of any other way.
I finished cleaning the front and the bathroom.
I heard that you can distinguish pets by their smell, so be careful.
Even my sweat has a floral fragrance.
It's almost time, so can you leave?
Sumire-chan, you're the worst!
It'll be fine. When visiting someone, it's common courtesy to arrive five minutes late.
Well, go for it…
He'll be going home at night, so don't pout like that.
I won't pout. My master's happiness is my happiness.
All lies.
Later.
Hasumi-senpai!
Oh… I… came a little early.
Were you busy?
Oh…
No… umm…
Let's go! Let's go home, sis.
Come on, Ran.
Hello.
See you later, Sumire.
Bye, thank you.
I'll be going now.
Wait, you…?
Have we met before?
I wonder…
I think your mind is just playing tricks, mister.
I have to go to my study school. Thanks for having us over.
Give your dog, Momo-chan, my regards.
Good day.
I guess it's just my mind playing tricks.
I'm sorry about that. My childhood friend suddenly decided to drop by.
No, I should apologize. I came too early myself.
The landlord let me in.
The landlord…
Oh! That's the dog, Momo-chan!
Thanks for having me.
Where do you intend to go from here?
I guess I'll just hang around the train station.
She's not the same woman I saw last time.
Did I make a mistake?!
What are you doing? Shimizu-san from No. 106!
Oh, nothing. Hello.
The weeds are growing so fast this season.
As soon as I pull out the ones on that side,
I have to work on this side. Then it's this side, that side.
Oh! Is that sukiyaki? With tofu?
No, I use potofu.
I see…
So actually, you truly value your master.
Well, of course. Since it's an honor that she's letting me stay there.
You're too modest.
Well, I have to match up to my rival, the golden retriever Momo.
The first Momo.
Yeah, I don't even get to have a picture taken.
Well, the first Momo was extraordinary. He was a purebred.
You know, if you keep comparing with extraordinary people,
I hear your child gets messed up too.
But he died early.
Around ten years old? Sumire thought it was her own fault and became so guilt-ridden.
She was crying constantly. I think it happened during middle school.
If you're going to make her cry someday, then I'd rather you left her early.
What are your feelings on that?
She'll probably be fine. I'm not loved enough to get cried over.
Let's see…
if you push this here like this…
"Hey, play with me more." is what it says.
This is interesting. No wonder it won an award.
No, Momo! Sorry, it doesn't know how to calm down.
Puppies are all like that.
When I heard its bark the last time, I thought it was a bigger dog.
Huh?
Oh…
Sometimes it barks like an adult, this little puppy.
But today, it's not at all vicious.
I wonder if it has taken a liking to me.
May I?
Oh, sure.
Wow, he's full of energy.
He has a cute face.
Oh, no! I'm so sorry! Please change out of it. I'll wash it right away.
I'll put a T-shirt right here.
Oh, obrigado.
Obrigado means Thank you in Portuguese.
I'm so unaffected whenever Momo's naked, but…
It'll be dry soon.
Thank you.
Since it's before your night duty, I guess coffee would be good?
Thanks.
Momo's sound asleep after running around so much.
Yes, seems like it.
Oh, it's already five o'clock.
Time goes by so fast.
I'm sorry things got a little panicky.
I'm happy that I can be with you like this, even for a moment.
Until just a while ago, you were on the other side of the earth and I couldn't even reach you.
Oh, hello.
Hello, thank you for letting me in.
Goodbye.
What a pleasant young man!
What a hypocritical old man.
I mean, don't you think his smile is too pleasant? It's too much.
I see your point.
But you have a pretty nice face yourself.
For real?
For real, you do!
Thanks, I feel really good now!
Really? That's great!
Wait a second…
Which floor is he from?
I'm home!
Yay! I have Sumire-chan all to myself!
I'm a bit tired.
Didn't you guys have fun?
Yeah.
A lot.
But I'm tired.
That sounds shady!
No, I haven't done anything like that. It was just… unsettling.
What do you want for dinner? I'll make you anything you want tonight.
Awesome! Omelette rice, then!
Gotcha. I'll go do some grocery shopping.
I'm happy!
Thanks for your hard work, my replacement.
Hey,
why was this thrown away?
Oh, sorry.
The bristles were bent and I thought it would be a good time to replace it.
I'll buy you a new one, what color would you like?
I want this one.
But you can't use that anymore.
What?
Nothing.
Expired, huh? Well, I guess everything has an end.
Oh hey,
I don't want omelette after all.
You can just make do with what you have, just don't leave.
No good?
All right. I won't go anywhere today.
As I thought, you write pretty good articles.
Successfully covering the costumes article and then a serious article afterward;
it's not something just anyone can do.
For me, the part where Kumango-kun shook hands with the children made me cry!
I was also given a very valuable experience.
I'm very grateful, really.
We're counting on you from now on too.
But don't slack off.
What decides your true worth is the next project.
I understand.
Please do your best.
Iwaya-san, Hasumi-kun is here for you.
Hello.
Do you have time today?
Yes. The general meeting is over.
Then…
As I thought, those two are seeing each other after all.
Yeah, Kuraki-chan's rumors were correct.
Well, that "cool and beauty" can only be fished by someone like him.
Thank you.
It seems like everyone at work already knows about us.
Fukushima-san also asked me about us.
Oh, Fukushima-san?
She said, "You two aren't going out by any chance, are you?"
So, since that day, I've been telling people that we're going out.
What an honest man…
Was that bad?
Oh, no. Not at all.
At the 7th block, there's a Mediterranean restaurant run by an acquaintance of mine.
It's not a very big restaurant, but would you like to go there?
Sure, that would be great.
I'm hungry, are you?
Yes.
People turn their heads at us.
When I'm with this man, I don't have to care about my height or educational background.
They're so picture perfect that it pisses me off.
I'm home!
Oh? The lights are off.
Momo?
Where are you?
Momo.
Momo, are you not here?
A picture?
What's that supposed to mean?
Where did you go?
To Sumire-chan
Iwaya-san!
Yes?
You're in charge of the medical story, right?
Yes.
Regarding this portion, we've discussed within our department,
should we change "neurons" to the Japanese word for neurons, to go with the rest of the story?
Oh, shall we do that?
I'll make the corrections.
Thank you, that'd be a great help.
I'm home.
I have a feeling that he might be lying somewhere unconscious again.
And hungry…
I doubt that.
He mentioned the last time that he got some money from his performance,
so he was going to buy milk on his own to drink.
Really?
Then maybe he was involved in an accident. Or in a hit-and-run and left dead in the mountains?
If you think about it logically, I doubt that too.
You think so?
Yes! He's a normal young man.
Just because he's missing a day or two doesn't mean anything.
I guess you're right.
Yes, I am!
Pets have their own pet lives too.
Be happy that you have some of your free life back again.
What if he found a new master?
You have a new man yourself! A really good catch, too!
That guy is only a pet, got it?
He is only a pet.
He may serve as family, but he's not human.
Hello?
This is Iwaya from Tokyo Newspaper.
Oh, Iwaya-san. Is this about your pet again?
What? How did you know?
I don't have time, so let's make this quick.
A pet is a very useful source for healing people.
They should also be loved.
But recently, there have been many masters who treat them as their own lovers or children.
That's very dangerous in several ways.
A pet is a pet.
If you go beyond that boundary and deepen your feelings,
your personal life will become unstable and your pet will also suffer.
That's how it is. Goodbye.
Sorry for the wait, Stephanie.
Bon appetit!
My Carlos disappeared.
Oh, really?
He has been gone for three days now. What should I do?
It's what they call pet loss, huh?
Kuraki-san, what kind of cat is it?
Huh, it's not like you.
What?
That you would worry about my cat.
You think so? She's always leaving early to take care of her own dog.
Huh? Oh, yes.
Well, if you pass out so many flyers, I'm sure it will be found.
You used the company copy machine, too!
It's okay! Don't be stingy, Ishida!
I don't think it'll be useful to distribute them in the office.
Has curly hair and is good at dancing.
Momo (male)
Not possible.
Hey, have you heard of that practice?
At your front door, you leave your pet's favorite food.
Under the dish you place a piece of paper that says: "Waiting. Come home."
And then your pet will come home.
Really?
It's a superstition.
But I live in an apartment…
I'm sorry!
Are you all right? Does it hurt somewhere?
I…
might get killed.
What?
He just rolled into my place like that…
Welcome home!
Sumire-chan, welcome back!
Welcome back! You're early! What's for dinner tonight?!
He was so quick to adapt to this place,
and he disappeared so easily too?
Maybe…
Was everything a dream until now?
Dance Company 21
Excuse me, I'm looking for someone. Do you know a Goda Takeshi?
Are you a fan of his?
You're Takeshi's…?
Excuse me?
Oh… umm…
He doesn't come here anymore, but…
Takeshi's acquaintance?
Yeah…
You came during the last performance too, didn't you?
Oh, really? Takeshi is no longer a member of our dance company.
Previously, he came in as a guest performer because I asked him.
Oh, I see.
Sometimes, Takeshi is also a "rental prince" in classical performances.
Opera position.
He's from a ballet school, so he has the talent to join any famous ballet company.
Opera position…
But I wonder if it's really that much of a handicap to be short in classical dance?
And…?
What do you want from Takeshi?
Huh?
Oh, umm. I'm—
Like she's something to Takeshi?
I'm asking, are you Takeshi's girl?!
Hey, Rumi.
It's okay. It's over between me and him.
Oh, no. It's nothing like that.
I'm a reporter, for Tokyo Newspaper.
I saw the performance the other day and
I wanted to ask Goda-san some questions.
But I'll try somewhere else. I'm sorry for bothering you.
Wait up!
You are pretty big…
Yes?
I think Takeshi will go back to your place.
Since he moved out of his house, he has never stayed at one place longer than a week, until now.
So, I just feel that he'll come back.
Why didn't you tell her?
That Takeshi has gone on that audition trip?
Well, if he hasn't told her himself, wouldn't it be weird if I did?
Plus, I don't know her either.
I gave up looking for him. It couldn't be helped.
We were together every day, yet I don't know anything about him.
But, I'm lost…
… without Momo.
I can't even remember what life was like without Momo.
Are you going to give up?
Yes. This time, it's my turn to wait.
I decided to wait.
So that Momo can come back at any time…
with his favorite food ready.
Yes, that's good.
Dear Sumire-chan, I will be gone for about two or three days.
Please don't worry.
If I come back with sad eyes, don't ask any questions and just pat my head.
If I come home smiling…
well, in that case, just pat my head too.
Well, I'll get going now.
Love, Momo.
The screening has finished, please stand up on stage.
Please take a seat.
Finalists of the International Contemporary Dance Auditions,
thank you for all your hard work.
As usual, they beat around the bush.
You have the confidence to go to Germany, don't you?
Yeah, probably.
Waiting. Come home.
I'm home.
Sumire-chan?
A dream?
It's okay if it's a dream.
I want to be with Momo.
That tickles.
Oh no…
I don't think I can stop.