Now port de bras.
Yeah, that's it.
Like you're sliding against the water.
Yes.
Madoka, you're not feeling the flow.
Feel the energy, everyone.
My name is Momo.
My parents are normal people, so obviously that isn't my name.
Though, I guess my name isn't that important. We'll just skip over it.
One month ago I was found unconscious.
Since then, I've been living at her house.
She is an elite Tokyo University graduate,
but her ex-boyfriend was jealous of her accomplishments and cheated on her.
Now she'll only date more successful men, tall guys with lots of money and fancy degrees.
Hasumi… senpai?
Welcome home!
I'm shorter than her and I don't have any money, but even so she's very kind to me.
Still, sex is not allowed.
Why? Because I'm just her pet.
Nice to see you, Master.
He looks very happy.
So much that it annoys me.
Hey, how long are you going to let him stay here?
I don't know.
What does this kid do during the day anyway?
Apparently he's been going to dance lessons lately.
If you're letting him eat for free, you should make him do some chores.
Yeah, I tried. But whatever it was, it didn't work.
When I make him cook, he cuts his finger.
If I make him clean up after himself, he breaks my Ginori plates.
Once I made him dry the futons, and he dropped them!
The landlord was furious!
Oh really?
Forget about him and listen. Hasumi-senpai is back in Japan!
Do you remember him? Back when I was still training to be a journalist in Kofu.
Umm, this concerns me more than your senior classmate.
This? Don't worry about it. I'm talking about my senpai here.
He's even hotter than he was four years ago.
So you think the unrequited love from four years ago will respark?
And I even found this.
Oh, this is from Kofu.
You two look cute together height-wise,
like a couple of friendly archaeologists too.
We were in the middle of research.
Did you meet and talk with him already?
I met him, but…
Hasumi… senpai?
Iwaya… right?
Long time no see. It's been what, four years?
Oh no, I mean…
Goodbye.
And my womanly pride got in the way again.
Oh, I figured it was your expressionless face. Like a Noh-mask.
Don't say Noh-mask.
Why don't you talk to him some more?
I wanted to, but you know I'm lousy at small talk.
And it was so unexpected. I was worried about my makeup.
I wasn't prepared, so I didn't want him to see me acting like an idiot.
Not after having been apart for so long.
See, you care too much about showing off.
That part of you is really unattractive, you know?
Well, excuse me.
I'm going to tell you straight.
Men prefer their girls ditzy and giggly to cool and successful.
That pisses me off.
Because it's a fact?
That's why I don't like men.
[sign]Kimi wa petto
You are my pet
[sign]2. A pet's effect
Oh, Miyamoto-san! Good morning!
Oh Takenouchi-san, let's cheer up!
Hey, you can't park here—
Oh, you're the new resident in 106! Was today your move-in date?
Yeah. I'm under your care now.
Oh no, thank you.
Should we back up the truck some more?
Yes.
Please back up the truck!
All right, all right!
Shut up…
Something hurts.
Good morning, Sumire-chan! Hey, I'm hungry.
Wait, why are you even in here?
I told you to stay out of my room!
Because I'm so hungry…
But if you're not going to make me any breakfast,
I'll just sleep here with you!
Like I'd let you…
So annoying…
I could've slept in till around two today. It's a late day for me.
I was only asleep for three hours. Why did I have to get up so early?
Don't put in any eggs. I think I'm developing an allergy to them.
How long are you planning on staying anyway?
Hmm… until you tell me to leave.
Next time you wake me up, I'll stuff you in a box and throw you away.
Here. Tada!
What's this?
I have a performance on the next holiday.
Performance? Oh, your dance?
Yeah. Will you come see it? I'm going to dance a solo.
It's neat, that you do this kind of stuff.
Hey, which name's yours, Momo?
Oh, this person's name is Goda Takeshi. Isn't that the same name as Jaian?
Nevermind the names. So can you come, please?
I don't know if I'll have the day off or not.
So you're not going to come?
I can't help it, I have a job.
It's hectic as it is because I just got transferred.
I couldn't get by if I had to fulfill your every wish at the same time.
Aw man.
You're lucky, pets can be so carefree.
You're not doing anything useful, so please don't ask to be spoiled.
Am I really that useless?
Yep, useless. I didn't know that kids these days were so weak.
You can't even properly carry the futons.
Oh, then if I can do sit-ups, will you come see me?
Why bother?
It's okay, I don't expect much from you anyway.
I'm just grateful you can take care of your own waste.
What are you doing, Momo?
The pose of repentance.
I saw it at Nikkou the other day.
I apologized, didn't I? So will you come see me?
Hey, see? I can even spin plates! Like this!
Don't break it! I'll go!
If I can.
Really?!
Awesome!
Oh, my Ginori plate!
That's why I love you, Sumire-chan!
Wait, stop…
SIT!
[sign]Tokyo Newspaper Company
Oh! That's him. The new guy, Hasumi-san.
Are you serious? That guy?
He's gorgeous!
I heard he's an elite coming from Rio de Janeiro,
and that he's even gotten an award from the Journalists Association.
Didn't he personally interview Brazil's president?
You're so lucky, Kuraki. You get to work in the same office.
[something missing here?]
I was starting to consider any single elite journalist,
even if they were a bit ugly,
but now…
Style!
Fashion!
Looks!
He's perfect!
I've got to go for him!
Just kidding.
That surprised me.
You're so silly, Fukushima-san!
Here is your coffee.
Thank you very much.
Tanaka knows the Social department inside and out.
Perhaps we can get information from him.
Oh and starting next month, we'll be working on a special project.
The first week will be…
Are you listening?
The first week will be on infertility, and it'll run over the next five weeks.
The members will be…
Why can't I be cute like that girl?
[sign]Four years ago
Thanks for coming, even though you had your own work.
Oh it's all right, I wasn't that busy or anything.
Take care.
Don't push yourself too much.
Umm…
Oh no, it's nothing…
Oh. All right.
I'm sorry.
Not at all…
Hey, let's take a picture for the occasion.
Oh, okay. I'll get it.
I'll take it now.
Excuse me, would you mind taking a picture for us?
Oh, sure thing.
Say cheese!
Thank you very much.
That time, too, I couldn't be true to my heart.
Oh, I'm sorry. My dog.
Wow, a female journalist in a hands-on research?
The diet project we did last time like that also was effective.
That Chemistry department journalist
is apparently your colleague, Iwaya-kun?
Yeah, that's true.
It was very good research,
but a smart person like you could probably write something even better.
How about it?
In the weekly, doing hands-on research on four mascot shows?
Iwaya-san in an animal suit?
Yes. This spring the Tokyo Familyland we sponsor is having
a grand reopening, and we've been asked to write about it.
This show is apparently especially popular.
I'll be looking forward to reading your work, Iwaya-kun.
The destiny of the Lifestyle department is in your elite journalistic hands.
We're counting on you, Iwaya-san!
Why do I have to dress in an animal suit?
Hello.
Are you tired?
Your forehead is wrinkled.
When you're tired, try imagining yourself stranded on an island.
Excuse me?
Close your eyes and picture a blue sea.
I really don't have time for this.
What's that? A malfunction?
And now you must live all by yourself on this island.
You're lonely, there's no sign of civilization, and the night is pitch black.
At times like this,
if you could've brought just one item with you, what would you choose?
Is this some form of counseling?
No, just a personal question.
Then excuse me, but I don't have time to talk right now,
or to waste on pointless fantasy.
If I were you, I would bring along my dog, Maron-chan.
What, a dog?
You'd want the kinds of things that can help in emergencies.
That's right. It's just like you to think that way, Iwaya-san.
Is that Chihuahua going to be of some use?
Yes. He's seen me through times of trouble.
Times of trouble?
I see.
I wonder what I would bring?
Maybe a phone.
Makes sense.
But I will need fire, so maybe a lighter?
I see.
You are a good person, Iwaya-san. Pretty, smart and responsible.
What, it's moving?
Wait a second, did you…
Next time, let's talk on the fourteenth floor.
Who are you, anyway?
That's enough, thank you.
I'm not so weak as to always have to depend on a counselor.
As you say, today's women have become stronger, for good or ill.
They didn't get that way on purpose though.
It just happened because they worked hard.
Once you have figured out an answer, please let me know.
What is most important to you as you try to survive on that island.
What? Umm—
In this world, everyone is stranded on their own island.
I have discovered an oasis.
Yes?
What? You've become a pet?
Yup, basically.
Pets get a place to stay and food for free.
Plus my owner is really pretty.
So basically,
you're a gigolo?
No, not a gigolo. Just a pet.
What? I don't get it. What do you mean by pet?
Hmm… kinda like that?
Like that?
Yeah. Aren't they cute?
Watching them revitalizes the spirit. That's how I am for her.
You say that, but…
I bet you've gotten laid.
Nope, not that.
You guys haven't done it?
No, we haven't.
Last time I just peeked at her while she was in the bathtub and I got a bloody nose for it.
She's actually pretty strong.
But if I get kicked out, I have nowhere to go. So I'm playing nice.
Who are you playing nice with, Takeshi?
I have a new dance move, will you try it for me?
Yes, sir.
Can I have a minute? Everyone, gather together.
So, is that master the reason you've been trying extra hard lately?
Me? Trying extra hard?
You beat me to that role for the upcoming performance.
Sorry, Junpei!
These are our image characters, Toto and Miyako.
I see.
By the way, how tall are you, Iwaya-san?
I'm a little over 170 cm.
Oh, you're pretty big. I guess there's only that one.
That one?
Hey, Koike-kun, could you bring that one?
That one? All right!
This is Toto's friend, Kumango-kun.
The eyes are all crooked.
As you can see, it's kind of a silly, klutzy character.
Wait, do you mean that this is for…
Well, we can't put you in the show right away, so let's have you walk around the park.
When you are wearing the costume, please move around constantly.
If you stand still, you'll just look like a standing decoration.
Please do your best.
Not just your hands, move your whole body.
You should exaggerate your actions, or you won't look like you're moving.
Yes, yes, like that.
Look, he tripped!
Are you dumb? You're so boring, stupid!
STUPID!
We know there's a human in there!
Let's take it off!
Yes, there's a human in here.
On three. One… two…
An elite Tokyo University graduate career woman.
Oh no, boys! Don't you feel sorry for Kumango-kun?
You little brats!
Run!!!
Wait, Kumango-kun! Hold on!
I'm home.
Welcome home, Sumire-chan!
Just now, on TV…
The parade is on everyday.
So let's everyone go to Tokyo Familyland!
Grand reopening during Golden Week!
What's wrong?
Nothing, I just wanted to change the channel.
I was just watching "Detective School Q"!
What, got a problem?
I want to know what's going on in the world.
I need to hear the news. I'm a journalist, you know.
Sorry.
Nevermind. My hip hurts.
What happened to your foot?
Oh, I just tripped during my lesson.
Did you go to the hospital?
No. I don't have my insurance papers with me right now.
You should go.
Don't worry about the money, what if a bone is broken?
Well, if you say you'll go with me, maybe I'll go.
Don't suck up to me, you know I'm busy with work.
It's just the hospital, go by yourself.
Man, that's cold.
You and I walking together out in the open is weird in the first place.
There's the age difference, plus I'm taller than you.
I don't like having to worry about what people are thinking.
Why don't you just tell them? Say that I'm your pet.
Are you joking? Just make sure you go.
Just make sure you move quickly.
This is going to be a big scoop.
What am I doing?
I'm hungry.
This is the best, Iwaya-kun!
The part about how you felt like you'd pass out from the lack of oxygen
makes the reader feel like they're right there with you.
Wow, I didn't know you couldn't
get on your feet on your own in those costumes.
Only an elite like you could
make a boring subject like this sound so interesting.
How about it? For this afternoon's parade,
we can have the Photography department go along with you.
That sounds great! We could take up more space for the article.
Why don't we stick Iwaya-san's picture and profile in there as well?
Good, good. If we stick a picture with her looking her usual
indifferent self next to the one of her in the costume…
Kind of like a before and after—
I don't think that will be necessary.
But…
I just wrote the article according to the instructions.
If you plan on featuring it any more than it is,
please specifically tell me the advantages of doing so.
If there are none, that'll be enough.
Umm, it was just a light joke.
I'm not accustomed to hearing jokes at my workplace.
How scary.
What a boring woman.
I just wanted to ask you something about a project you've previously worked on, but…
you seem a little busy.
Hey, isn't that Hasumi-kun? How is External Affairs?
Oh, hello. It's definitely different.
Here, there are no incidents like the demonstrations in Venezuela.
I'm still feeling my way around.
Well, your work has been centered on South America.
I understand that, but…
I need to learn to think more on the global level.
"Global level."
Well, well, an expert journalist from South America definitely has a broad view.
Yeah, that global whatever sounds like a good word.
I didn't know, but we kind of transferred in and out at the same time, huh?
Yes, due to the circumstances…
I heard. It must've been a pretty hard punch?
Whatever do you mean by that?
Sorry, that didn't come out right…
Thank you for your hard work.
Likewise.
Are you okay?
What?
I can see the patch on your hip.
They make you wear an animal costume as soon as you've transferred, it's no surprise.
Yes, I've been learning a lot.
Everything can be chalked up as an experience.
Do you really think that way?
This is just bullying.
Don't you know?
As soon as talk about your transfer came up,
the English newspaper department asked for you right away.
What do you mean?
But for some reason, they stuck you in our department.
They purposely threw you in a dead end position.
How come you know all this?
I just have very good hearing.
I also heard today from the External Affairs department
that they're going to have a celebration for Hasumi-san's arrival.
I think I will go check it out.
Men are really afraid of women getting more powerful than them.
If you want to have things go your way, it's more advantageous to act dumb and cute.
Well, I suppose that would be too embarrassing for a Tokyo University graduate like you.
This is just bullying.
I knew it anyway.
I knew, I just pretended not to notice.
I've just been doing my best.
You're not very good at being a woman.
They purposely put you in a place where you couldn't advance your career.
I've earned everything with my own hands, from my university to my job.
If you want to have things go your way, it's more advantageous to act dumb and cute.
Are they saying all that effort was for nothing?
Don't push yourself too much.
See, you tried to show off again.
You're really a boring woman.
That's not what I mean. Sorry.
I'm such a weak person.
Welcome home!
I came home in a taxi.
What happened?
I didn't want anyone to see my face.
You're kidding! Why?
Don't laugh at me!
Don't laugh.
Don't you laugh!
It's okay.
You're always so cool, Sumire-chan.
You're a good cook,
you're hardworking and you're always doing your best.
There.
You look pretty again.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Thanks, Momo.
Let's go to the hospital.
Tomorrow, together.
Really?
I can take you to an abandoned island, too.
An abandoned island?
If I have you with me, it'll probably be fun.
Shoot, where did I put my cell phone?
Ah man, how boring.
Hello, this is Iwaya.
Hello, this is Hasumi from External Affairs.
Sorry to call you so late. Is this time okay for you?
Oh, are you still at work?
Did you call to consult me about that project you're working on?
Oh, no, no. That's not a problem anymore.
I just wanted to apologize for earlier today.
Oh, don't worry about that. It was my fault.
I'm relieved.
It's just that you stormed out, so I kind of panicked.
Not at all, I'm sorry.
Oh yeah, I just got some tickets to a Noh performance.
Noh?
Yeah. It's for tomorrow at noon. Do you think you could go?
Tomorrow?
To put it bluntly, I'm asking you on a date.
Yes, I understand.
I'm glad.
So tomorrow, at 1 pm, at Ginza Five.
Yes, thank you. Goodbye.
What happened?
Sorry, I have work tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
I'm sorry. I can't go to the hospital with you.
Oh, that's okay. I had some stuff to do tomorrow anyway.
Really?
Yeah.
Sorry.
It's okay, it can't be helped.
We can go the day after.
It's all right. I'm fine.
Sorry.
Forget about it. I'm hungry!
Oh, it completely slipped my mind. I wonder if there's anything left over.
What? Make something quick!
I'll make it now.
Should it have been shorter?
But I wouldn't want him to thing I was trying too hard to look young.
Hey!
We still have about half an hour. Would you like to get some tea?
Sure.
Hey?
Fukushima-san.
Hello.
Iwaya-san and Hasumi-san? Wow, what a coincidence!
Really!
Fukushima-san gave me the tickets.
Oh, is that so?
Wait a second, are you two going out or something?
Oh no, nothing of that sort.
Of course not!
He just came back to Japan!
Why would such a great guy like Hasumi-san have to find a girl so quickly?
It's not quite like that.
Iwaya-san's just an old friend, right?
I hoped you would ask me to come with you.
Oh, really?
I didn't notice that at all.
Let's go, the four of us together.
We have tickets too.
Our seats are right next to yours.
Wow, I'm so happy! I get to sit with Hasumi-san!
Yeah, see?
A heavy battle between the pro-wrestlers…
In this situation, if I had to choose, I'd rather go see that.
"Must-see fight?"
That's a grammatical mistake…
Because they're sloppy with things like that, pro-wrestling fans are looked down on.
No?
Man.
I have a performance on the next holiday.
Will you come see it? I'm going to dance a solo.
Damn. It's today!
And I was talking about going to the hospital when the performance was today.
What's wrong?
Umm, I… My pet…
Your pet?
My pet got injured…
He can't go to the hospital by himself and umm…
I've got to go home!
I'm sorry, I'm going home! Please enjoy yourselves.
I'm really very sorry, senpai!
What is that?
Are you really going to be okay?
Yes, I'll be fine.
Are you sure?
You're really going to be able to do this?
I'm depending on you.
Gotcha.
I'm going to go make sure Junpei knows the B part well.
All right.
Let's go.
Excuse me. Nobody is allowed back here before the performance!
There you are, Momo!
Why didn't you tell me?
What did you come here for?
Huh? What do you mean?
You had a date, didn't you? With a guy from work?
Wait a minute, how do you know that?
I don't know, I could just tell.
Then why didn't you tell me that tonight was your performance?
Because you looked so happy.
Who you choose to spend your time with is up to you,
but when you lied, it pissed me off.
You didn't go to the hospital, did you?
Nope.
But they took out some of the jumps and lifts so it shouldn't be too bad.
And I have to take the responsibility, since I'm the one who injured it.
Momo…
Takeshi!
Let's go.
Okay.
Pay for the ticket to see my performance.
All right, let's go.
Momo. His real name is Takeshi.
Wow.
Thank you for your hard work! You looked so cool!
Thank you.
You're really the best. Please accept this.
Oh, you didn't have to. Thank you very much.
Great job! May I shake your hand? Thank you so much!
Thank you, I wonder what's inside?
He almost seems like a different person.
Sumire-chan!
They told me to refrain from too much strenuous activity.
Can you bathe me again?
Sure.
After your bath, I'll put some ice on your foot.
That's thoughtful of you.
I'm glad I came.
You were the best out of all of them, Momo.
You think so?
Yup, I was really surprised.
It would have been even better if I hadn't been injured.
Hey. You're not going to scold me?
You don't like being seen like this in public, right?
I wish I could have given you a big bouquet of flowers too.
Okay, time to go!
All right, let's go home. Sumire-chan, gimme a piggyback ride.
What are you talking about, Momo?
Have a safe trip home.
You're kidding me.
That was a good movie.
Yes.
I'm really sorry about earlier today.
It's fine, you really don't have to apologize so many times.
Oh, but I have to apologize myself.
What?
People have been calling you a Noh mask?
How did you know that?
Oh, Fukushima-san and her friend told me earlier.
I'm sorry, it was an inconsiderate choice for a date.
Not at all!
I like them! I really do, Noh masks and kokeshi dolls.
Some things about you haven't changed a bit.
To tell the truth,
when I first met you in the elevator,
I was a bit surprised.
You had become so beautiful.
But I'm relieved.
Inside, you're still the same as back then.
You're smart, but afraid to be yourself. Hardworking, but clumsy…
Do you think so?
Yes, that's how you are.
Oh, and remember that last day in Kofu?
When I told you we should take a picture,
you said "yes" and tried to take it yourself.
I laugh every time I remember that.
I'm really sorry about that.
The way you always apologize hasn't changed, either.
I was happy.
That day,
when you came to see me off in your work clothes.
I dunno, I just felt really happy.
It's kinda late, but…
Umm…
I'm also… very happy.
I can't put it into words well, but…
I'm happy that you invited me to the Noh performance,
and the way we can walk together like this.
I'll walk you back to your place.
Yes, thank you so much.
Wait…
home?
Wow, so you live here?|this is where you live?
Yeah. Well, good night.
Eh?
I'm sorry, here is fine for tonight.
Iwaya-san from the fourth floor!
What?
You dropped your futon blankets again! Please don't do this.
Oh, I'll help carry them up.
Are you sure? Thank you very much.
Please be careful from now on.
Yes.
You were drying quite a lot, huh?
What?
Oh, yeah. I'm sorry, I had many guests.
Here is fine, really.
Don't worry about it, I can bring them to your front door.
Where?
Thank you very much!
Really, you were a great help.
So, that's it. Good night.
What I've really been trying to say…
All day, really, is that…
Since you came to see me off, four years ago…
No, from even before that…
I've been thinking about you.
I was with you all this time, but I couldn't get it out.
I tried to forget you.
But…
Coming back…
And meeting you again after four years…
The moment I saw you,
I just felt like I had to make you mine.
Hasumi-senpa—
Mo—
Momo, be quiet!